<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rewards &#8211; TheFinancials</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thefinancials.net/rewards/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:50:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Toyota Launches 100 Cars for Good Program 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-toyota-global-com-toyota-100-cars-for-good-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-toyota-global-com-toyota-100-cars-for-good-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1136</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.toyota-global.com to check how Toyota is going to meet its social responsibilities. It is an initiative by Facebook that deals with marketing or giving away of a hundred cars in hundred days to all NGOS. What happens is each voter has to choose few organizations that may receive the cars from the program. The platform [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-toyota-global-com-toyota-100-cars-for-good-program/">Toyota Launches 100 Cars for Good Program 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.toyota-global.com</em></span> to check how Toyota is going to meet its social responsibilities. It is an initiative by Facebook that deals with marketing or <strong>giving away</strong> of a hundred cars in hundred days to all NGOS. What happens is each voter has to choose <strong>few organizations </strong>that may receive the cars from the program. The platform that receives maximum votes will get a brand new car.</p>
<h2>www.toyota-global.com &#8211; Program Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>Users from the US are eligible for this program. For frequent updates-users are required to follow the <a href="http://www.facebook.com/toyota">Facebook page</a>. Winners are revealed on the page by making announcements in the time span of seventy-two hours.</p>
<h4>How One can Apply in the Toyota 100 Cars for Good Program</h4>
<ol>
<li>Users are required to <strong>apply in the months</strong> of April and March. The last date to apply if March 12th. A large number of nonprofit organizations submit their applications explaining their demands of the need of vehicle.</li>
<li>Reviewing occurs in the month of March specifically the 26th of March. An independent group is gets the duty for a <strong>panel work</strong> where they assess and analyze all submissions. Each applicant is a certified one with a great number of organizations being chosen for as finalists.</li>
<li><strong>Getting Ready</strong> on April 10th for the offers or announcements. In a program where finalists were announced, each organization received details regarding the program. In the meantime, they got updated regarding the attractive offers by Toyota.</li>
<li>Voting is to begin in the month of May with May 14 as the specific day. It the <strong>time for voters</strong> to vote for the desired organization. Voting is done by logging on to the Facebook account.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-toyota-global-com-toyota-100-cars-for-good-program/">Toyota Launches 100 Cars for Good Program 2016</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-toyota-global-com-toyota-100-cars-for-good-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Join Starbucks Rewards Gold Program For Free Drinks &#038; Food</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-starbucks-com-starbucks-rewards-gold-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-starbucks-com-starbucks-rewards-gold-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1128</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.starbucks.com &#8211; one can join Starbucks Rewards Gold program to get some free drinks, food and more items. You can visit website to find terms &#38; benefits. It is a well-known company that is recognized as the best sellers’ for coffee. The chain of coffee houses in Seattle, Washington. Starbucks is considered to be the [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-starbucks-com-starbucks-rewards-gold-program/">Join Starbucks Rewards Gold Program For Free Drinks &#038; Food</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.starbucks.com</em></span> &#8211; one can join Starbucks Rewards Gold program to get some free drinks, food and more items. You can visit website to find terms &amp; benefits. It is a well-known company that is recognized as the best sellers’ for coffee. The chain of coffee houses in Seattle, Washington.</p>
<p>Starbucks is considered to be the largest company in a coffee house business in the whole world. With about nineteen thousand seven hundred and sixty-three stores in about fifty-nine countries, Starbucks is reaching sky levels. An <strong>interactive relationship</strong> with farmers helps them facilitate in high coffee yields.</p>
<h2>www.starbucks.com &#8211; Program Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>Having a Starbucks card is the initial step of the process of getting a gold level account. It is followed by joining the rewards program later. Each time a person pays for a coffee with his or her card, he <strong>earns a point</strong>. This point appears in the form of a star. Collecting a number of thirty stars within a period of twelve months gets us set up to the level of gold for a year with</p>
<ul>
<li>A free drink and points for every twelve stars</li>
<li>Gold Card that too is personalized</li>
</ul>
<h6>Specialized offers for Members of Starbucks Rewards Gold Program</h6>
<p>Once gold, always a gold. For this is what the Starbucks has to stay for all the Gold users out there. Once a gold member achieves the level, he or she has to <strong>get thirty stars</strong> to maintain his level. If a person fails to qualify for the golden level till the anniversary date (the date when he got qualified) arrives, he will be dropped down to the <strong>lower level</strong> that is a green level in this case.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-starbucks-com-starbucks-rewards-gold-program/">Join Starbucks Rewards Gold Program For Free Drinks &#038; Food</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-starbucks-com-starbucks-rewards-gold-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Earn Some Money With E-Rewards Opinion Panel by Answering Surveys</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-e-rewards-com-e-rewards-opinion-panel/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-e-rewards-com-e-rewards-opinion-panel/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1135</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.e-rewards.com to check out the possible options to earn money with E-Rewards Opinion Panel by answering simple questions. Visit website for terms &#38; conditions. E-Rewards was founded in 1999 by Hal Brierley and Mort Meyerson. It is headquartered in Plano, Texas. There are the more than the 1200 employees working at the offices in different [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-e-rewards-com-e-rewards-opinion-panel/">Earn Some Money With E-Rewards Opinion Panel by Answering Surveys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.e-rewards.com</em></span> to check out the possible options to earn money with <em><strong>E-Rewards Opinion Panel</strong></em> by answering simple questions. Visit website for terms &amp; conditions.</p>
<p>E-Rewards was founded in 1999 by Hal Brierley and Mort Meyerson. It is headquartered in Plano, Texas. There are the more than the 1200 employees working at the offices in different countries around the world.</p>
<h2><em>www.e-rewards.com</em> &#8211; Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>Getting confused about where to go for Dinner? Now, there is no need to think a lot about. E-rewards Opinion Panel helps  you to find your <strong>favorite restaurant</strong> and also enrolled in the e-rewards program. Through this program, the customers can get the different items as a reward by redeeming the e-rewards currency.</p>
<p>In order to join the e-rewards, the customers should have the invitation given by the sponsors. The customers must be <strong>more</strong> than the age of <strong>13 years</strong> and also should be a legal resident of the United States, Guam or Puerto Rico.</p>
<h6>Join E-rewards Program</h6>
<p>After receiving the invitation for joining the E-rewards program, the customers should have to follow the given below steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>First of all, go to <a href="http://www.e-rewards.com/">www.e-rewards.com</a>.</li>
<li>The customers have to select their country and language.</li>
<li>On the next page, they have to log into their e-rewards account by entering their email address and password.</li>
<li>In the case of <strong>forgetting</strong> the password, the customer has to click on the option “Forgot Password”.</li>
<li>Once the process of logging in has been completed, the customers will be able to redeem the e-rewards currency online and get amazing rewards.</li>
</ol>
<p>In order to get any kind of information, visit the <a href="http://www.e-rewards.com/memberservices.do.">FAQ page</a> of e-rewards</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-e-rewards-com-e-rewards-opinion-panel/">Earn Some Money With E-Rewards Opinion Panel by Answering Surveys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-e-rewards-com-e-rewards-opinion-panel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How A Member Can Earn More Credit with Total Rewards Program</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-totalrewards-com-earn-more-credit-with-total-rewards-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-totalrewards-com-earn-more-credit-with-total-rewards-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 15:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1134</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.totalrewards.com to learn to get more credit with Total Rewards program while you play, dine, shop or stay at Total resorts &#38; casinos see terms. It is a loyalty program or a system that deals with credit card services that may aid hotel, games and other shopping services or facilities. Known as total Gold in [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-totalrewards-com-earn-more-credit-with-total-rewards-program/">How A Member Can Earn More Credit with Total Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.totalrewards.com</em></span> to learn to get more credit with <em><strong>Total Rewards program</strong></em> while you play, dine, shop or stay at Total resorts &amp; casinos see terms. It is a loyalty program or a system that deals with credit card services that may aid hotel, games and other shopping services or facilities. Known as total Gold in the <strong>initial stages</strong> of development, it was later termed as Total Rewards.</p>
<h2>www.totalrewards.com &#8211; Intro &amp; Features<strong><br />
</strong></h2>
<p>On becoming a member of the Total Rewards Program, a user can get unlimited offers loaded up to the credit card services. They have a four tier system as follows</p>
<ul>
<li>Gold</li>
<li>Platinum</li>
<li>Diamond</li>
<li>Seven Stars</li>
</ul>
<p>The more credits earned will benefit a user with more rewards. It can also earn a person a number of bonus points</p>
<h4>Become a Member &amp; Start Saving with Total Rewards Program</h4>
<p>The question lies in the fact that how can one becomes an <strong>efficient member</strong> of such a fruitful program. It can be done by following these points:</p>
<ul>
<li>Search the official website and sign up for an account</li>
<li>For the <strong>sign-up</strong>, one is required to fill in his personal details that include name, email id, phone number etc.</li>
<li>Enter a required password.</li>
<li>Complete the Security queries.</li>
<li>Enter the given captcha or code.</li>
<li>Click on the create account</li>
</ul>
<h6>Ways to Earn Reward Credits</h6>
<p>There are a number of <strong>ways to win</strong> or earn rewards. These include:</p>
<ol>
<li>Slot machines</li>
<li>Table games</li>
<li>Dining, hotel, leisure experiences</li>
<li>Energy plus is kind of bonus points</li>
<li>Facebook has Caesar’s Casino option.</li>
<li>The Total Rewards Visa Card</li>
</ol>
<p>One can also <strong>redeem</strong> his or her points to get additional benefits. These additional benefits are for all those people who earn points.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-totalrewards-com-earn-more-credit-with-total-rewards-program/">How A Member Can Earn More Credit with Total Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-totalrewards-com-earn-more-credit-with-total-rewards-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat Fresh &#038; Live Healthy Life With Subway Freshbuzz Rewards Program</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-subwayfreshbuzz-com-subway-freshbuzz-rewards-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-subwayfreshbuzz-com-subway-freshbuzz-rewards-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 15:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1133</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.subwayfreshbuzz.com to find out all the latest offers about food items with Subway Freshbuzz Rewards program, enroll today and see the terms of service. The history of Subway dates back to 1965 and current stats denote that it is one of the world’s largest franchises. www.subwayfreshbuzz.com &#8211; About &#38; Intro It has more than thirty-four [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-subwayfreshbuzz-com-subway-freshbuzz-rewards-program/">Eat Fresh &#038; Live Healthy Life With Subway Freshbuzz Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.subwayfreshbuzz.com</em></span> to find out all the latest offers about food items with Subway Freshbuzz Rewards program, enroll today and see the terms of service. The history of Subway dates back to 1965 and current stats denote that it is one of the world’s largest franchises.</p>
<h2>www.subwayfreshbuzz.com &#8211; About &amp; Intro</h2>
<p>It has more than <strong>thirty-four thousand</strong> locations in around ninety-one countries. It is a submarine sandwich franchise that attracts an audience because of the ever yummy spice of flavors added to the <strong>aroma of the food</strong> products they serve the customers with. The services add to the high ranking of the Subway Company and help them reach sky level of success with the passage of time.</p>
<h4>How to Shop With Subway Freshbuzz Rewards Program &#8211; Guide</h4>
<ol>
<li>Subway fresh buzz is actually a <strong>scheme of discounts</strong> or various offers for all the subscribers or to more precision, to all the food lovers out there.</li>
<li>The official website aids and facilitates the customer to stay updated with the latest deals and offers.</li>
<li>It&#8217;s either a person registers online to the website or gets registered using his or her phone. After registration, one is required to enter a code (2 codes per day at max). This is how they get access to the levels of rewards.</li>
<li>The specially marked <strong>three ounces</strong> cup will help a person level up to the second and third level. Level three is the superhero level where one can be eligible to win a grand prize.</li>
<li>Official <strong>rules and terms</strong> are available online for all customers and they are required to follow them up.</li>
<li>In addition to all offers, the super creamy food is by all means a favorite for all foodies out there.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-subwayfreshbuzz-com-subway-freshbuzz-rewards-program/">Eat Fresh &#038; Live Healthy Life With Subway Freshbuzz Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-subwayfreshbuzz-com-subway-freshbuzz-rewards-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn to Shop &#038; Earn With Best Buy Reward Zone Program</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/bestbuyrewardzone-ca-best-buy-rewards-zone-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/bestbuyrewardzone-ca-best-buy-rewards-zone-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1130</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Bestbuyrewardzone.ca &#8211; You can earn and save while shopping with Best Buy Rewards Zone program, find out how it works. Redeem &#38; check rewards status. Best buy is the American multinational consumer electronics company founded in 1966. It is headquartered in the Richfield, Minneapolis. It has the more than 125,000 employees working at about 1050 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/bestbuyrewardzone-ca-best-buy-rewards-zone-program/">Learn to Shop &#038; Earn With Best Buy Reward Zone Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>Bestbuyrewardzone.ca</em></span> &#8211; You can earn and save while shopping with Best Buy Rewards Zone program, find out how it works. Redeem &amp; check rewards status. Best buy is the American multinational consumer electronics company founded in 1966. It is headquartered in the Richfield, Minneapolis.</p>
<p>It has the more than 125,000 employees working at about 1050 locations in different countries around the world like China, Canada, Europe, Mexico and the United States.</p>
<h2>Bestbuyrewardzone.ca &#8211; Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>Best Buy is offering the Best Buy Reward Zone Program to its customers. Now, the customers of the Best Buy have a great chance to earn the points and get the money. They just have to <strong>join the Best Buy Reward Zone Program</strong>. After joining the program, the customers will be able to earn the 1 point on the each dollar spent at Best Buy. Whenever the customers have stock 250 points, they can get the $5.</p>
<h4>How to Join the Best Buy Rewards Zone Program</h4>
<p>The customers just have to enroll in the reward zone program to enjoy the special offers. The whole process to join the reward zone is as follows</p>
<ul>
<li>Visit the <strong>website</strong> of best buy reward zone <a href="http://www.bestbuy.com/">http://www.bestbuy.com/</a>.</li>
<li>Click on the option “Get Started” to proceed forward.</li>
<li>If any customers already have the <strong>membership</strong> of the best buy, then they just have to provide their phone number, member number and also zip code.</li>
<li>If they don’t already have a membership, then click on the option “Enroll”.</li>
<li>The customers have to provide the basic personal information that is required on the page.</li>
<li>After <strong>submitting</strong> the information, the customers can use their account and enjoy the various benefits of the reward zone program.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/bestbuyrewardzone-ca-best-buy-rewards-zone-program/">Learn to Shop &#038; Earn With Best Buy Reward Zone Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/bestbuyrewardzone-ca-best-buy-rewards-zone-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Enroll in myStonyfield Rewards Program</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mystonyfieldrewards-com-mystonyfield/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mystonyfieldrewards-com-mystonyfield/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 14:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1132</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Stonyfield launches a reward program, learn how to redeem &#38; check status of rewards with my Stony Field rewards program, find out details &#38; info here.  Located in New Hampshire in the United States of America, Stony Field is an organic yogurt manufacturer company. Stonyfield &#8211; Rewards Program Intro &#38; Features It has a history [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mystonyfieldrewards-com-mystonyfield/">How to Enroll in myStonyfield Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>Stonyfield</strong> </em>launches a reward program, learn how to redeem &amp; check status of rewards with my Stony Field rewards program, find out details &amp; info here.  Located in New Hampshire in the United States of America, Stony Field is an organic yogurt manufacturer company.</p>
<h2>Stonyfield &#8211; Rewards Program Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>It has a history that dates back to 1983 when the Stonyfield farm was founded by Samuel Kymen. He found it as an organic farming school. The company claims to produce the best of <strong>organic yogurt</strong> in the United States. Moreover, new invention in the world of Stonyfield is the <strong>smoothie</strong> that comes with a foil less cap and can be carried with ease.</p>
<h4>How Redeem Rewards from myStonyfield Rewards Program &#8211; Guide</h4>
<p>In order to get facilitated by the StonyField rewards, one is required to follow up the following steps carefully:</p>
<ol>
<li>Search for any <strong>reward code</strong> on the product packaging. It can be anywhere.</li>
<li>Visit the official website and signup for a rewards account.</li>
<li>Sign into the <strong>specified account</strong> and enter the codes to the online account.</li>
<li>After entering the code, one can save and redeem points the way he wants to.</li>
</ol>
<p>Stonyfield purchases can help the users earn fruitful rewards. My Stonyfield reward got its extension due to immense audience response.</p>
<p>So it is advisable to keep eating the products and entering the codes so as to get the points. MyStonyField is known to be offering the <strong>biggest bargain</strong> in town that aids all users to get access to the organic food products and baby products too and what not it helps to aid all the non-profit organizations, hence proving to be the best choice for all customers out there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mystonyfieldrewards-com-mystonyfield/">How to Enroll in myStonyfield Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mystonyfieldrewards-com-mystonyfield/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Earn and Save with Wyndham Rewards Program</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-wyndhamrewards-com-wyndham-rewards-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-wyndhamrewards-com-wyndham-rewards-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1129</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.wyndhamrewards.com for Wyndham Rewards Program, it is a travel rebates program which aims to increase the loyalty. Find how to redeem &#38; apply for rewards. It is a company or a worldwide leading domain that has to deal with a number of hotels and restaurants in the United States. The history dates back to 2006 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-wyndhamrewards-com-wyndham-rewards-program/">How to Earn and Save with Wyndham Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.wyndhamrewards.com</em></span> for <em><strong>Wyndham Rewards Program</strong></em>, it is a travel rebates program which aims to increase the loyalty. Find how to redeem &amp; apply for rewards. It is a company or a worldwide leading domain that has to deal with a number of hotels and restaurants in the United States.</p>
<p>The history dates back to 2006 when it was founded and today it has an approximate amount of seven thousand and four hundred <strong>hotels and resorts</strong> that are spread across sixty-six countries in the six continents.</p>
<h2>www.wyndhamrewards.com &#8211; Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>Wyndham Worldwide program has brought forward a reward program. In order to be a member, following steps need to be followed</p>
<ol>
<li>Search for the online website and join it by clicking the joining option.</li>
<li>Personal details are to be entered at the required place. Details include name, contact number, email ids etc.</li>
<li>Creating a username with required info is the next step followed by setting a password.</li>
<li>Next step is to choose the <strong>preferences</strong> for earning reward points.</li>
<li>Ticking the box to receive frequent emails is optional but is highly recommended so as to stay updated.</li>
<li>Going through the terms and conditions by the company is a necessary step and needs to be read carefully before clicking the join in button.</li>
<li>As a member, the account can be easily accessed, anytime and anywhere in the world.</li>
</ol>
<h6>Procedure to Earn Points</h6>
<p>There is a way step to get access to points includes the following</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Buying points:</strong> If a user has no enough points for reward he has an option of buying the points so as to achieve the desired reward.</li>
<li><strong>Special deals</strong> and offers are also available</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-wyndhamrewards-com-wyndham-rewards-program/">How to Earn and Save with Wyndham Rewards Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-wyndhamrewards-com-wyndham-rewards-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Save on HeartBurn Treatment with Prevacid 24HR Coupon</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-prevacid24hr-com-prevacid-24hr-coupon/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-prevacid24hr-com-prevacid-24hr-coupon/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 20:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1073</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.prevacid24hr.com to save money on heart-burning treatment, if doctor recommends Prevacid 24HR then use Prevacid 24HR coupon. Prevacid is the over-the-counter medicine for the Heartburn, approved by the FDA (U.S Food and Drug Administration). Prevacid 24HR is the Proton Pump Inhibitor (PPI). www.prevacid24hr.com &#8211; Intro &#38; Features It has been available in the United States [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-prevacid24hr-com-prevacid-24hr-coupon/">Save on HeartBurn Treatment with Prevacid 24HR Coupon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.prevacid24hr.com</em></span> to save money on heart-burning treatment, if doctor recommends Prevacid 24HR then use <em><strong>Prevacid 24HR coupon</strong></em>. Prevacid is the over-the-counter <strong>medicine</strong> for the Heartburn, approved by the FDA (U.S Food and Drug Administration). Prevacid 24HR is the <strong>Proton Pump Inhibitor</strong> (PPI).</p>
<h2>www.prevacid24hr.com &#8211; Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>It has been available in the United States and Australia marketed by the Novartis and Pfizer respectively. Its official website is <a href="http://www.prevacid24hr.com/">www.prevacid24hr.com</a>. If you are facing the Heartburn for a long time and your doctor <strong>suggests</strong> you Prevacid 24HR, then you have the great chance to save on the Prevacid 24HR products. You just have to download the Prevacid 24HR Coupon from the website.</p>
<p>The customers can get the coupon through two ways. They can either contact Prevacid 24HR customer relations at <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">1-800-452-0051</span> </em>and get the coupon through the mail or also <strong>print </strong>the coupon and can <strong>save $5</strong> by clicking on the option “Save $5 Now” available at <a href="https://www.prevacid24hr.com/prevacid24hr-coupon/">Official Website</a>.</p>
<h4>How to Register For Prevacid 24HR Perks Program</h4>
<p>In order to participate in the Prevacid 24HR Perks Program, the customers have to visit and <strong>sign up</strong> at <a href="http://www.prevacid24hr.com/">www.prevacid24hr.com</a>. The customers should be more than the age of 18 years and also be the resident of the United States and District of Columbia. The complete process to register is as follows:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to <a href="http://www.prevacid24hr.com/">www.prevacid24hr.com</a> and sign up by entering a name, address, email address, password and date of birth. Also, the customer needs to <strong>answer</strong> the few simple survey questions.</li>
<li>Then, click on the option “Enter”.</li>
<li>Enter the UPC code present at the Prevacid 24 HR product and also select the pack size.</li>
<li>In the last, click on the option <strong>“Redeem”</strong> and get the Claim Code through email.</li>
<li>Get the reward by using the claim code on the reward provider`s website.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-prevacid24hr-com-prevacid-24hr-coupon/">Save on HeartBurn Treatment with Prevacid 24HR Coupon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-prevacid24hr-com-prevacid-24hr-coupon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kroger Digital Coupon will Give 2X Fuel Points at Purchases on Kroger</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-kroger-comsummerfuel-kroger-digital-coupon/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-kroger-comsummerfuel-kroger-digital-coupon/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 19:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rewards]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=1072</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Use Kroger Digital coupon to get double fuel points while purchases at Kroger grocery store. Visit www.kroger.com/Summerfuel &#38; see program terms. You must be familiar with the largest chain grocery stores in the United States “Kroger Co.”. With the experience of the more than 130 years, Kroger Co. www.thekrogerco.com is serving the millions of customers [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-kroger-comsummerfuel-kroger-digital-coupon/">Kroger Digital Coupon will Give 2X Fuel Points at Purchases on Kroger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Use <strong><em>Kroger Digital coupon</em> </strong>to get double fuel points while purchases at Kroger grocery store. Visit www.kroger.com/Summerfuel &amp; see program terms. You must be familiar with the <strong>largest chain</strong> grocery stores in the United States “Kroger Co.”.</p>
<p>With the <strong>experience</strong> of the more than 130 years, Kroger Co. <a href="http://www.thekrogerco.com/">www.thekrogerco.com</a> is serving the millions of customers worldwide. There are more than 343,000 employees working at the <strong>790 grocery stores</strong>, 344 jewelry stores and also 1,200 fuel centers.</p>
<h2>Kroger Digital Coupon &#8211; Intro &amp; Features</h2>
<p>The customers of the Kroger can <strong>earn the points</strong> by purchasing at the Kroger stores and use those points to save money at the fuel stations. Now, the customers can also earn the Double Fuel Points with the help of the Kroger Digital Coupon. The customers can save the <strong>10¢ per gallon</strong> by purchasing at Kroger Fuel Centers. The customers will get the 1 fuel point for the each dollar spent at the grocery store. And also they will get the 2 fuel points for the each dollar spent on the purchase of gift cards.</p>
<p>The customers must have the plus card in order to earn the fuel points. For the Double Fuel Points, the customers have to <strong>download</strong> the Kroger Digital Coupon. Once the Kroger Digital coupon has been downloaded, the customer will be able to earn the double <strong>fuel points</strong> on the purchases at grocery stores.</p>
<h6>How to Download Kroger Digital Coupon Online</h6>
<ol>
<li>First of all, the customers have to <strong>sign-in</strong> to their account at Kroger or if they don’t have one, then they need to create a new account.</li>
<li>After signing in, click the option <strong>“Load to Card”</strong>.</li>
<li>Download the Kroger Digital Coupon from the website.</li>
<li>Just that. Now the customers can start earning double fuel points on Friday to Sunday every week.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-kroger-comsummerfuel-kroger-digital-coupon/">Kroger Digital Coupon will Give 2X Fuel Points at Purchases on Kroger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-kroger-comsummerfuel-kroger-digital-coupon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
