<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Featured &#8211; TheFinancials</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thefinancials.net/featured-2/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:50:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Monopoly Game At Safeway: Shop &#038; Get a Chance to Win $200 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 23:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguidance.info/?p=3974</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Visit www.playmonopoly.us to play, while shop Safeway Monopoly rare pieces to increase your chance to win a prize with Monopoly game board 2017-2018. The Monopoly Game Out at Safeway! You can play Safeway&#8217;s monopoly game 2/8 &#8211; 5/9 to get a chance for winning a prize money of up to $200,000,000. Moreover, beside to this [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/">Monopoly Game At Safeway: Shop &#038; Get a Chance to Win $200 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Visit <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.playmonopoly.us</em></span> to play, while shop <em><strong>Safeway Monopoly rare pieces</strong></em> to increase your chance to win a prize with Monopoly game board 2017-2018. The Monopoly Game Out at Safeway! You can play Safeway&#8217;s monopoly game 2/8 &#8211; 5/9 to get a chance for winning a <em><strong>prize money of up to $200,000,000</strong></em>. Moreover, beside to this prize money, there is also a list of money saving offers. You have to play the game at <a href="http://www.PlayMonopoly.us/"><em>www.PlayMonopoly.us</em></a> website.</p>
<p>In addition to it, one also needs to buy Monopoly game boards from participating Safeway stores. After that, buy some qualifying game items for which you will receive a ticket at each buying.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-3977" src="https://www.theguidance.info/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly.jpg" alt="Safeway Monopoly" width="695" height="358" srcset="https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly.jpg 695w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly-300x155@2x.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></p>
<p>You have to collect your tickets to add to your Safeway Monopoly board and get a chance to win a prize. A wide <em><strong>range of prizes includes</strong> </em>gift cards, homes, cars, cash, vacations and much more. The details are available as below. If you want to win the biggest prize then try to collect rare pieces of the game.</p>
<p>The Safeway Monopoly 2017 &#8211; 2018&#8217;s <em><strong>prize money game ends</strong></em> on earlier of May 9, 2018, OR on the date at which all the tickets will finish. Each of us has about 3 months for playing the game which starts from 8 February.</p>
<p><em><strong>[UPDATE: February 17, 2017]</strong></em></p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #999999;"><em>www.playmonopoly.us</em></span> is not working and giving an error of 403 forbidden for some users. This can be due to your location because some markets are out of qualifying area. Here is a list of states which are outside of the eligible area. (Arizona, Arkansas, Alaska, California, Connecticut, Colorado, District of Columbia, Delaware, Hawaii, Idaho, Illinois, Iowa, Indiana, Louisiana, Maine, Montana, Maryland, Massachusetts, Nevada, Nebraska, New Hampshire, New Mexico, New Jersey, New York, North Dakota, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, South Dakota, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Wyoming or Washington)</p>
<h2>www.playmonopoly.us &#8211; How to Play Monopoly Game</h2>
<p>The 2017 Prize game is organized at about 2,325 participating locations. These locations comprise a number of big names under it including. Carrs, Safeway, Pavilions, Randalls, Vons, Eagle, Pak ‘n Save, Jewel-Osco, Tom Thumb, ACME Markets, United Supermarkets, Shaw’s/Star Market, Market Street, Amigos, Albertsons Market®, United Express, Lucky (Southern California only) and Super Saver.</p>
<p>To <strong><em>PlayMonopoly login</em> </strong>is must for all the players who want to play the game with other online community. If anyone wants to <em><strong>Play Monopoly Online</strong></em> then he/she can create an account online at the official website. Have some fun and enjoy the game play with your opponents from all over the world.</p>
<p>You have to put the purchased game tickets on the exact matching place at the Monopoly game boards. Be careful at this step as you have to place the game markers on the accurate matching prize play area. For this just moisten the back side of strip or game marker and patch it on the game board.</p>
<h4>Other Ways to Win Prize:</h4>
<p>Beside to above, there are some other ways to win prizes with Safeway Monopoly game. Each ticket has a special offer or discount. This offer can include any of these, MONOPOLY Online Code, Instant Win Grocery Gift Card, Nickelodeon Online Code, 2 free game tickets, Instant Win Cash, OR Free Product Coupon.</p>
<h6>How to Win with these Codes</h6>
<p>Login to <span style="color: #999999;"><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">www.playmonopoly.us</span></em></span> and then click on the Monopoly online game logo OR Nickelodeon Online Game Logo. This depends on the type of coupon code you are entering at <span style="color: #808080;"><em>www.playmonopoly.com</em></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Now follow the instructions as it appears on your screen. Enter the code when it asks for in the steps.</li>
<li>You can also enter the code on the application available for iOS and Android devices. Just follow the directions on your screen.</li>
<li>Finally, the site will reveal the winner of the prize at the specified date.</li>
</ul>
<h6>2nd Chance Sweepstakes</h6>
<p>Drawings will be held randomly from all the online entered codes and codes entered via emails. These drawings will be separate for each of Sponsor&#8217;s 14 Divisions. (ACME, Eastern, Denver, Houston, Intermountain, Jewel-Osco, Northern California, Portland, Shaw’s, Seattle, Southwest, Southern California, and United) The drawings will be held on February 15, February 22, March 1, March 8, March 15, March 22, March 29, April 6, April 12, April 19, April 26, May 3, and May 10, 2017. Each winner from each division will receive a $1,000 grocery gift card.</p>
<p>Beside to above, in a bonus drawing, 1 winner from each division will be selected for the following prizes. February 22, 2017 – $5,000 Grocery Gift Card; March 7, 2017 – $10,000 Family Vacation Prize; April 26, 2017 – $20,000 College Tuition Prize; and June 2, 2017 – $40,000 Home Makeover Prize.</p>
<h6>How to Enter in Draw via Mail</h6>
<ul>
<li>Stick on your MONOPOLY Online Coupon Code to a 3&#8243; X 5&#8243; index card.</li>
<li>Write up your name, address, (including city, state and zip code), phone number, age and add your official signature on the card.</li>
<li>Now mail your entry by hand addressed the envelope to 2nd Chance Sweepstakes, P.O. Box 441208, Kennesaw, GA 30160.</li>
</ul>
<h6>Progressive Jackpot</h6>
<ul>
<li>100 Monopoly online coupon codes are eligible to win the Progressive Jackpot. The Progressive Jackpot amount will continue to increase on the website over the time.</li>
<li>The progressive jackpot will start at $1,000 and will continue to grow until the jackpot code is entered on the website and is won by someone. After which the amount will revert to $1,000 and then again starts to grow.</li>
</ul>
<h6>Hawaii&#8217;s Own Sweepstakes</h6>
<p>Each of the coupons entered online will automatically be submitted to a random drawing. The winner will get a chance to win one Hawaii Vacation.</p>
<h6>Last Chance Drawing</h6>
<p>If top 6 prizes will not be claimed by anyone up to 30, May 2017. ONLY THEN a random drawing will be conducted named as (LAST CHANCE DRAWING) in which all valid MONOPOLY 2nd chance sweepstakes entries occur on or about June 12, 2017, for one $1,000,000 Cash (30-year annuity) Prize.</p>
<h6>Nickelodeon Sweepstakes</h6>
<p>When anyone registers, and play Nickelodeon game then each coupon submitted will be entered into a random drawing. The participant will get a chance to win one of 3 Family Vacation for four to the Nickelodeon Resort in Punta Cana, Dominican Republic.</p>
<h5>Win Over $200 Million In Prizes And Money Saving Offers</h5>
<p>Game Board Prizes (1,753,271 Prizes; total ARV $24,005,000)</p>
<ul>
<li>(3) $1,000,000 Cash</li>
<li>(3) $1,000,000 Vacation Home</li>
<li>(15) $100,000 Cash or Luxury Car</li>
<li>(25) $40,000 Home Makeover</li>
<li>(25) $35,000 Vehicle of Your Choice</li>
<li>(50) $20,000 College Tuition</li>
<li>(50) $10,000 4-Wheeler</li>
<li>(50) $10,000 Family Vacation</li>
<li>(50) $5,000 Cash</li>
<li>(100) $1,500 Gas Grill &amp; Groceries</li>
<li>(100) $1,500 LED HD TV</li>
<li>(100) $1,000 Cash</li>
<li>(100) $1,000 Laptop Computer</li>
<li>(600) $300 Smart Watch</li>
<li>(50) $5,000 Groceries</li>
<li>(100) $1,000 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(350) $500 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(750) $200 Family Picnic</li>
<li>(2,500) $100 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(5,000) $50 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Gift Card Mall</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Fandango Gift Card</li>
<li>(25,000) $15 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(37,500) $10 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(800,000) $5 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(750) $200 Cash</li>
<li>(2,500) $100 Cash</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Cash</li>
<li>(37,500) $10 Cash</li>
<li>(800,000) $5 Cash</li>
</ul>
<h5>Instant Win Prizes (172,017,713 Prizes; total ARV $505,904,934)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(3) prizes of $10,000 Cash</li>
<li>(5) prizes of $5,000 Cash</li>
<li>(234,155) Grocery Gift Card prizes of $5,000, $1,000, $100, $50, $25, $10 and $5</li>
<li>(30,000) $25 Special Gift Card prizes from Burger King, MasterCard, Visa, Macy’s, GAP, JCPenney, Microsoft Xbox, AMC Theaters, Fandango, Nike and Regal Cinemas</li>
<li>(2,000) $20 Special Gift Card prizes from Domino’s</li>
<li>(14,000,000) prizes $24.99 Rouxbe Cooking School Class</li>
<li>(97,751,550) Free Product Prizes</li>
<li>(60,000,000) Two Free Game Tickets</li>
</ul>
<h5>Instant Discount Offers (58,350,000 Discounts, total ARV $681,802,500)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(9,000,000) $29.99 Shutterfly Photo Book</li>
<li>(4,750,000) $15.15 Shutterfly Prints</li>
<li>(9,750,000) $14.99 Shutterfly Shopping Bag</li>
<li>(4,750,000) $8.99 Shutterfly Magnet</li>
<li>(2,500,000) Let Life Bloom $10 e-gift certificates</li>
<li>(25,000,000) Let Life Bloom $5 e-gift certificates</li>
<li>(50,000) $10 off $100 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(75,000) $5 off $50 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(100,000) $2 off $20 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(2,375,000) Let Life Bloom Discounts of 15%</li>
</ul>
<h5>Online Game Prizes (325,338,010 Prizes; total ARV $36,959,250)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(10) $10,000 Cash Prizes</li>
<li>(38,000) Grocery Gift Card Prizes ranging from $25 to $1,000</li>
<li>(1,000,000) $24.99 Rouxbe Cooking School Class Prizes</li>
<li>(300,000) $21.99 Nickelodeon 40-pack Special Edition Oliver labels</li>
<li>(600,000) $5 Nickelodeon 12 count Special Edition Mini Oliver’s labels</li>
<li>(272,500,000) Fandango Reward Tokens</li>
<li>(180,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Dora’s Big Buddy Race through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Kate! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Pablo! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Naiya! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Emma! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Alana! through Google Play</li>
<li>(50,000,000) Two Free Game Tickets</li>
</ul>
<h5>Online Discount Offers (72,985,000 Discounts, total ARV: $56,590,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(1,000,000) $29.99 Shutterfly Photo Book discount offers</li>
<li>(5,000,000) Let Life Bloom $5 e-gift certificate</li>
<li>(20,000) $10 off $100 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(40,000) $5 off $50 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(100,000) $2 off $20 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(1,000,000) General Mills Box Tops for Education</li>
<li>(40,000,000) Nickelodeon downloadable Activity Sheets</li>
<li>(24,000,000) Nickelodeon Digital Game Codes</li>
<li>(900,000) Nickelodeon TMNT (Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles) Digital Game Codes</li>
<li>(925,000) Nickelodeon Oliver’s Labels Discounts of 30%, 40% or 50%</li>
</ul>
<h5>Cents off Coupons (304,546,450 Coupons; total ARV: $182,423,324)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Cents off coupons ranging from 50¢ to $5 with 107 different coupons with an average of 59.9¢.</li>
</ul>
<h5>2nd Chance Sweepstakes (238 Prizes; total ARV: $1,232,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(182) $1,000 Grocery Gift Card Prize</li>
<li>(14) $5,000 Grocery Gift Card Prize</li>
<li>(14) $10,000 Family Vacation Prize</li>
<li>(14) $20,000 College Tuition Prize</li>
<li>(14) $40,000 Home Makeover Prize</li>
</ul>
<h5>Nickelodeon Sweepstakes (3 Prizes; total ARV: $30,150)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Family Vacation for four (two adults and two children) to the Nickelodeon Resort in Punta Cana, Dominican Republic. This sweepstakes prize will include airfare, resort accommodations for four nights and $4,000 in cash.</li>
</ul>
<h5>Hawaii’s Own Sweepstakes (2 Prizes; total ARV: $14,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Hawaii Vacation for Two to the Waikiki Parc Hotel in Honolulu, Hawaii. This sweepstakes prize will include airfare, resort accommodations for five nights and $2,500 in cash.</li>
</ul>
<h5>Progressive Jackpot (100 Prizes; total ARV: $250,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Progressive Jackpot prizes begin at $1,000 with a maximum total value of $250,000.</li>
</ul>
<h5>Last Chance Drawing</h5>
<ul>
<li>(1) $1,000,000 Cash (30-year annuity) Prize</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/">Monopoly Game At Safeway: Shop &#038; Get a Chance to Win $200 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
