<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Entertainment &#8211; TheFinancials</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thefinancials.net/entertainment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:50:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>PlayatMcD.com: How to Win With McDonalds Monopoly Game Promotion</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/playatmcd-com-win-mcdonalds-monopoly-game-promotion/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/playatmcd-com-win-mcdonalds-monopoly-game-promotion/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 19:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguidance.info/?p=4519</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Visit PlayatMcD.com to participate in the promotion by McDonald&#8217;s for their customers. McDonalds Monopoly Game is its one of the most popular promotions. This year promotion will start in March and ends in April for In-Restaurant Participants, while ends in May for online participants. PlayatMcD.com &#8211; How to Play the Game There are total 513,591,720 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/playatmcd-com-win-mcdonalds-monopoly-game-promotion/">PlayatMcD.com: How to Win With McDonalds Monopoly Game Promotion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Visit <strong><em>PlayatMcD.com</em></strong> to participate in the promotion by McDonald&#8217;s for their customers. McDonalds Monopoly Game is its one of the most popular promotions. <strong>This year promotion will start</strong> in March and ends in April for In-Restaurant Participants, while ends in May for online participants.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-4520" src="https://www.theguidance.info/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/PlayatMCD.jpg" alt="PlayatMcD.com" width="695" height="358" srcset="https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/PlayatMCD.jpg 695w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/PlayatMCD-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/PlayatMCD-300x155@2x.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></p>
<h2>PlayatMcD.com &#8211; How to Play the Game</h2>
<p>There are total 513,591,720 pieces of the game are available for the participants of all 50 states of the United States, District of Columbia, Saipan, and Guam. <strong>Every Game Piece</strong> has 2 Game Stamps. These stamps can be one from Food Prize, Instant Win, OR Collect &amp; Win Stamps. There are about 131,879,647 Food Prize Stamps while 23,040 Instant Win stamps for distribution.</p>
<p>To get Game Pieces simply buy the specific menu item from the participating McDonald&#8217;s restaurant. The <strong>menu items eligible for this promotion</strong> include Big Mac Sandwich, Medium Fountain Drinks, 10-piece Chicken McNuggets, Hash Browns, Filet-O-Fish Sandwich, McMuffin Sandwiches, and Biscuit Sandwiches. Game Pieces are attached to specifically marked packaging furthermore, the Game Stamps should be peeled off gently to reveal the printing.</p>
<p>There is another way to get Game Pieces, especially for the people who can&#8217;t spend huge money to buy them. You can mail a self-addressed, <strong>stamped envelope with postage</strong> and your home address. Send the envelope to P.O. Box 49248, Strongsville, OH 44149-0248.</p>
<p>The Prize related to <strong>Food Stamps</strong> can be redeemed from any of the McDonald&#8217;s Restaurant participating in the promotion. If you have an <strong>Instant Win game stamp</strong> then you can claim the prize you won at <a href="http://www.iwonatmcd.com/">www.iwonatmcd.com</a> official website.</p>
<p>While the <strong>Collect &amp; Win stamps</strong> provide you different MONOPOLY properties, you have to collect a specific combination to win a prize. To download the Monopoly game board visit <em><span style="color: #0000ff;">www.playatmcd.com</span></em> this will help you to identify and track properties and railroads.</p>
<h4>How to Enter the Promotion at PlayatMcD.com</h4>
<p>If you want to participate in the game then simply register at the website <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.PlayatMcD.com</em></span> or at the McDonald&#8217;s App. Each customer can register either with the help of code or not. The registered users can then enter into the promotion online and can <strong>submit up to 10 codes in a day</strong>. There are total 5 different periods of online survey submission, the details are as following;</p>
<ul>
<li>1st round begins at 12:00 a.m. ET on 29, March and ends at 11:59:59 p.m. ET on 4, April.</li>
<li>The 2nd period begins at 12:00 a.m. ET on 5, April and ends at 11:59:59 p.m. ET on 11, April.</li>
<li>The 3rd period begins at 12:00 a.m. ET on 12, April and ends at 11:59:59 p.m. ET on 18, April.</li>
<li>While the 4th round begins at 12:00:00 a.m. ET on 19, April and ends at 11:59:59 p.m. ET on 25, April.</li>
<li>At last, 5th period starts at 12:00:00 a.m. ET on 29, March and ends at 11:59:59 p.m. ET on 9, May.</li>
</ul>
<h4></h4>
<h4>Prizes of PlayatMcD.com Promotion</h4>
<p><strong>Food Prizes</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Medium Size Fries</li>
<li>Small Size McCafé Frappé or Smoothie</li>
<li>Regular Size McFlurry</li>
<li>Quarter Pounder with Cheese or Premium Buttermilk Crispy Chicken Sandwich</li>
<li>McGriddles</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Instant Win Prizes</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>$25 In Cash (Total 11,500 winners)</li>
<li>$50 In Cash (Total 11,540 winners)</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Collect &amp; Win Prizes</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>$50 In Cash (Total 4,500 winners)</li>
<li>$500 In Cash (Total 200 winners)</li>
<li>$1,000 In Cash (Total 10 winners)</li>
<li>$2,000 In Cash (Total 10 winners)</li>
<li>$5,000 In Cash (Total 5 winners)</li>
<li>$10,000 In Cash (Total 5 winners)</li>
<li>$25,000 In Cash (Total 5 winners)</li>
<li>$50,000 In Cash (Total 5 winners)</li>
<li>$1,000,000 In Cash (Just 1 winner)</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Online Sweepstakes Prizes</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>$50,000 In Cash (Total 5 winners – 1 Winner per Entry Period)</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/playatmcd-com-win-mcdonalds-monopoly-game-promotion/">PlayatMcD.com: How to Win With McDonalds Monopoly Game Promotion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/playatmcd-com-win-mcdonalds-monopoly-game-promotion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>USCellular.com/12Days: Win With US Cellular 12 Days Promotion</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/uscellular-com-12days-promotion-sweepstakes/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/uscellular-com-12days-promotion-sweepstakes/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 13:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguidance.info/?p=4512</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Open USCellular.com/12Days if you want to earn with US Cellular 12 days of giveaways sweepstakes. U.S. Cellular just announced this sweepstakes right after the launch of Match &#38; Win IWG by Tracfone and Selfie Sweepstakes by Cricket Wireless. It&#8217;s an online promotion in which anyone can participate at www.USCellular.com/12Days. If you are a customer of [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/uscellular-com-12days-promotion-sweepstakes/">USCellular.com/12Days: Win With US Cellular 12 Days Promotion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Open <em><span style="color: #0000ff;">USCellular.com/12Days</span></em> if you want to earn with US Cellular 12 days of giveaways sweepstakes. U.S. Cellular just announced this sweepstakes right after the launch of Match &amp; Win IWG by Tracfone and Selfie Sweepstakes by Cricket Wireless.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s an online promotion in which anyone can participate at <strong><em>www.USCellular.com/12Days</em></strong>. If you are a customer of US Cellular then you are eligible for this survey. This promotion will begin in the holiday season if you are a resident at any one of 50 states of America OR District of Columbia. Then <em><strong>you are eligible to take part</strong></em> in this promotion. However, you must be at least 18 years old while taking part in this survey.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-4513 size-full" src="https://www.theguidance.info/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/USCellular.jpg" alt="USCellular.com/12Days" width="695" height="358" srcset="https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/USCellular.jpg 695w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/USCellular-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/USCellular-300x155@2x.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></p>
<p>Although the registration period starts on November 16. However, they will start giving away from December 1st with the tech-related items at weekdays only. Furthermore, the <strong>final drawings of the grand prize</strong> will be done on December 18. The prizes of worth more than $20,000 will be awarded during the month from the popular tech brands including Samsung, JBL, and LG.</p>
<h2>Visit USCellular.com/12Days to Enter</h2>
<p>You can open <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><em>USCellular.com/12Days</em></span> and then follow the steps to complete the registration form. To increase the chances of winning you can simply complete the registration form on daily basis. This will <strong>increase the chances of winning the grand prize</strong> at the final drawings.</p>
<p>Starting from December 1st, every customer of US Cellular is invited at <span style="color: #808080;"><em>USCellular.com/12Days</em></span> to play the game. The more you play the game the more there is the chance to win the game. The result will be displayed immediately if you win or not. Each time you play the game, you will automatically enter as a participant to win Grand Prize.</p>
<h4>List of USCellular.com/12Days Promotion Prizes</h4>
<p>There are total 114 Prizes, which are distributed in a sequence of 12 Prizes Per Weekdays. The prizes will be awarded randomly and the list of the prize with day and date is as followings.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Day 1 (Dec. 1):</strong> Samsung LEVEL ON On-Ear Headphones</li>
<li><strong>(Dec. 2) Day 2:</strong> JBL Clip+ Portable Bluetooth Speakers</li>
<li><strong>Day 3 (Dec. 3):</strong> Plantronics Backbeat FIT Wireless Headphones</li>
<li><strong>(Dec. 4) Day 4:</strong> Transcend 64GB MicroSD Cards</li>
<li><strong>Day 5 (Dec. 7):</strong> Samsung Level U Wireless Headphones</li>
<li><strong>Day 6 (Dec. 8):</strong> Jawbone UP MOVE Activity Trackers</li>
<li><strong>(Dec. 9) Day 7:</strong> Braven 705 Wireless HD Bluetooth Speakers</li>
<li><strong>Day 8 (Dec. 10):</strong> LG TONE PRO Wireless Stereo Headsets</li>
<li><strong>Day 9 (Dec. 11):</strong> Garmin Vívosmart Activity Trackers</li>
<li><strong>Day 10 (Dec. 14):</strong> JBL Flip 3 Wireless Bluetooth Speakers</li>
<li><strong>(Dec. 15) Day 11:</strong> Pure.gear PureJuice Portable Chargers</li>
<li><strong>Day 12 (Dec. 16):</strong> Withings Activité Pop Watches</li>
</ul>
<p>At the end of the Promotion, the winner of <span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Grand Prize</strong> </span>will get a big deal of HOME PRIZE which will worth about $7,500. The Grand Prize will comprise of the following items.</p>
<ul>
<li>1 &#8211; LG 60″ Class UHD Smart LED TV</li>
<li>Only 1 &#8211; LG 4.1 ch 360W Music Flow Wi-Fi streaming Sound Bar</li>
<li>1 &#8211; LG Blu-ray Disc Player with streaming services and built-in Wi-Fi</li>
<li>5 &#8211; LG G Pad 8.0 tablets</li>
<li>1 &#8211; Samsung Counter Depth Side-By-Side Stainless Steel Refrigerator</li>
<li>Only 1 &#8211; Samsung Over the Range Stainless Steel Microwave</li>
<li>1 &#8211; Samsung Stainless Steel Free Standing Gas Range with Convection</li>
<li>1 &#8211; Samsung Stainless Steel Built-In Top Control Dishwasher</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/uscellular-com-12days-promotion-sweepstakes/">USCellular.com/12Days: Win With US Cellular 12 Days Promotion</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/uscellular-com-12days-promotion-sweepstakes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yoplait.com/100ways: Get a Chance to Win $100,000 with Yoplait 100 Ways</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/yoplait-com-100-ways/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/yoplait-com-100-ways/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 16:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguidance.info/?p=4145</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Open Yoplait.com/100ways at your browser and enter the Yoplait100Ways Code from the lid. Once you successfully register for the contest, you are now eligible to get a chance to win $100,000 via 100ways program. No matter which flavor is your favorite one, Yoplait Greek Whip, Yoplait Original Strawberry, OR Yoplait Light. The Yoplait.com/100ways Code is printed [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/yoplait-com-100-ways/">Yoplait.com/100ways: Get a Chance to Win $100,000 with Yoplait 100 Ways</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Open <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>Yoplait.com/100ways </em></span>at your browser and enter the <em><strong>Yoplait100Ways</strong> </em>Code from the lid. Once you successfully register for the contest, you are now eligible to get a chance to <em><strong>win $100,000</strong></em> via 100ways program. No matter which flavor is your favorite one, Yoplait Greek Whip, Yoplait Original Strawberry, OR Yoplait Light.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-4146 size-full" src="https://www.theguidance.info/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Yoplait-100-Ways.jpg" alt="yoplait.com/100ways" width="695" height="358" srcset="https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Yoplait-100-Ways.jpg 695w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Yoplait-100-Ways-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Yoplait-100-Ways-300x155@2x.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></p>
<p>The <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Yoplait.com/100ways</span></em> <em><strong>Code</strong></em> is printed on the lids of the pack, to increase the chance of the winning game. Buy more Yoplait Yogurts and stuff up your fridge with delightful flavors of yogurt. One hundred ways to Yoplait is a scheme with which a lucky person is going to be richer with an amount of $100,000 in just a minute. Beside to jackpot prize, Yoplait is also giving hundreds and thousands of prizes on daily basis.</p>
<h2>Yoplait.com/100ways &#8211; Tips to Win</h2>
<p>To enter into Sweepstakes, there are just a few steps. It&#8217;s quite easy to enter into the Yoplait promotion. Just follow the steps available as below and participate in the survey.</p>
<h5>Step 1: Get Yoplait 100 Ways Code</h5>
<p>On the top of the Yoplait Yogurt pack, you can find a 5-digit alphanumeric code on the top of your lid. If you have got a Multi-Pack, then the code is printed on the box. The Yoplait products with special marks are available during this promotion period. This period starts from July 7, 2017, to May 15, 2018.</p>
<p><em><strong>You can also request a code with the help of any of the following methods.</strong></em></p>
<ul>
<li>Mail a 3&#8243; X 5&#8243; piece of paper with your full name, mailing address and phone number to this address. 100s of ways to <span style="color: #999999;"><em>Yoplait, c/o HelloWorld, P.O. Box 5046, Department: 825562, Kalamazoo, MI 49003-5046</em></span>.</li>
<li>Send an email to <span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #999999;"><em>100sofwaystoYoplait@epiinc.com</em></span> while don&#8217;t forget to write up &#8216;100 of ways to Yoplait &#8211; Code Request&#8217; in the subject line.</li>
</ul>
<p>You will receive your code via email from Yoplait within 48 hours after you requested for the code.</p>
<h5>Step 2: Visit Yoplait.com/100ways to Enroll in Survey</h5>
<p>After collecting the code, open the website at <span style="color: #0000ff;">www.yoplait.com/100ways</span> to register yourself and then follow the steps. Connect with Facebook account and fill-up the complete form as it appears on the screen.</p>
<h5>Step 3: Submit Your Purchase Code</h5>
<p>After successful registration, you are then invited to <strong>submit your purchase code</strong> on the next screen. At this screen, you just have to enter the Yogurt flavor along with your Yoplait code.</p>
<h5>Step 4: Check The Progress Bar</h5>
<p>Each time you submit a code, you will see your ranking on the next screen.</p>
<p>Moreover, you can also share your ranking status with your Social friends on <span style="color: #808080;"><em>Facebook</em></span>, <span style="color: #808080;">Twitter</span> or <span style="color: #808080;">Pinterest</span>!</p>
<h5>Step 5: Enter Codes as Much as You Can</h5>
<p>The more the number of codes you register, the greater the chance to win the prize of $100,000. The best method is just to enter as many different flavors as you can. You can <strong>submit up to 5 codes</strong> <strong>in one day</strong>. If you want to get an extra entry, then upload one Yoplait Selfie in the gallery and you will get one entry. Furthermore, if you submit a Yoplait poll once in a month then, you will also get an entry in sweepstakes. Besides to all above, if you complete &#8216;How do you Yoplait?&#8217; Quiz then you will get an entry for sweepstakes.</p>
<h5>Somethings to Know Before You Join In</h5>
<ul>
<li>This promotion is open only for the legal residents of the 50 U.S. States For at least 18Years Old.</li>
<li>Each person can enter up to 5 Lid codes per day during the whole promotion period.</li>
<li>The <strong>Jackpot amount (100,000)</strong> is only available for 1 Winner.</li>
<li><strong>Instant Win Game</strong> winners number is 3,652.</li>
<li><strong>Total value of Prizes</strong> is $178,260.</li>
<li>Hello, World is administrating this promotion while General Mills is sponsoring it.</li>
</ul>
<p>Now you know all the basic rules of the game, you are welcome to Yoplait promotion. Join in at <a href="http://www.yoplait.com/100ways">www.yoplait.com/100ways</a> and Good Luck for your journey.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/yoplait-com-100-ways/">Yoplait.com/100ways: Get a Chance to Win $100,000 with Yoplait 100 Ways</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/yoplait-com-100-ways/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monopoly Game At Safeway: Shop &#038; Get a Chance to Win $200 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 23:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Featured]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguidance.info/?p=3974</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Visit www.playmonopoly.us to play, while shop Safeway Monopoly rare pieces to increase your chance to win a prize with Monopoly game board 2017-2018. The Monopoly Game Out at Safeway! You can play Safeway&#8217;s monopoly game 2/8 &#8211; 5/9 to get a chance for winning a prize money of up to $200,000,000. Moreover, beside to this [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/">Monopoly Game At Safeway: Shop &#038; Get a Chance to Win $200 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Visit <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.playmonopoly.us</em></span> to play, while shop <em><strong>Safeway Monopoly rare pieces</strong></em> to increase your chance to win a prize with Monopoly game board 2017-2018. The Monopoly Game Out at Safeway! You can play Safeway&#8217;s monopoly game 2/8 &#8211; 5/9 to get a chance for winning a <em><strong>prize money of up to $200,000,000</strong></em>. Moreover, beside to this prize money, there is also a list of money saving offers. You have to play the game at <a href="http://www.PlayMonopoly.us/"><em>www.PlayMonopoly.us</em></a> website.</p>
<p>In addition to it, one also needs to buy Monopoly game boards from participating Safeway stores. After that, buy some qualifying game items for which you will receive a ticket at each buying.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-3977" src="https://www.theguidance.info/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly.jpg" alt="Safeway Monopoly" width="695" height="358" srcset="https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly.jpg 695w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Safeway-Monopoly-300x155@2x.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></p>
<p>You have to collect your tickets to add to your Safeway Monopoly board and get a chance to win a prize. A wide <em><strong>range of prizes includes</strong> </em>gift cards, homes, cars, cash, vacations and much more. The details are available as below. If you want to win the biggest prize then try to collect rare pieces of the game.</p>
<p>The Safeway Monopoly 2017 &#8211; 2018&#8217;s <em><strong>prize money game ends</strong></em> on earlier of May 9, 2018, OR on the date at which all the tickets will finish. Each of us has about 3 months for playing the game which starts from 8 February.</p>
<p><em><strong>[UPDATE: February 17, 2017]</strong></em></p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline; color: #999999;"><em>www.playmonopoly.us</em></span> is not working and giving an error of 403 forbidden for some users. This can be due to your location because some markets are out of qualifying area. Here is a list of states which are outside of the eligible area. (Arizona, Arkansas, Alaska, California, Connecticut, Colorado, District of Columbia, Delaware, Hawaii, Idaho, Illinois, Iowa, Indiana, Louisiana, Maine, Montana, Maryland, Massachusetts, Nevada, Nebraska, New Hampshire, New Mexico, New Jersey, New York, North Dakota, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, South Dakota, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Wyoming or Washington)</p>
<h2>www.playmonopoly.us &#8211; How to Play Monopoly Game</h2>
<p>The 2017 Prize game is organized at about 2,325 participating locations. These locations comprise a number of big names under it including. Carrs, Safeway, Pavilions, Randalls, Vons, Eagle, Pak ‘n Save, Jewel-Osco, Tom Thumb, ACME Markets, United Supermarkets, Shaw’s/Star Market, Market Street, Amigos, Albertsons Market®, United Express, Lucky (Southern California only) and Super Saver.</p>
<p>To <strong><em>PlayMonopoly login</em> </strong>is must for all the players who want to play the game with other online community. If anyone wants to <em><strong>Play Monopoly Online</strong></em> then he/she can create an account online at the official website. Have some fun and enjoy the game play with your opponents from all over the world.</p>
<p>You have to put the purchased game tickets on the exact matching place at the Monopoly game boards. Be careful at this step as you have to place the game markers on the accurate matching prize play area. For this just moisten the back side of strip or game marker and patch it on the game board.</p>
<h4>Other Ways to Win Prize:</h4>
<p>Beside to above, there are some other ways to win prizes with Safeway Monopoly game. Each ticket has a special offer or discount. This offer can include any of these, MONOPOLY Online Code, Instant Win Grocery Gift Card, Nickelodeon Online Code, 2 free game tickets, Instant Win Cash, OR Free Product Coupon.</p>
<h6>How to Win with these Codes</h6>
<p>Login to <span style="color: #999999;"><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">www.playmonopoly.us</span></em></span> and then click on the Monopoly online game logo OR Nickelodeon Online Game Logo. This depends on the type of coupon code you are entering at <span style="color: #808080;"><em>www.playmonopoly.com</em></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Now follow the instructions as it appears on your screen. Enter the code when it asks for in the steps.</li>
<li>You can also enter the code on the application available for iOS and Android devices. Just follow the directions on your screen.</li>
<li>Finally, the site will reveal the winner of the prize at the specified date.</li>
</ul>
<h6>2nd Chance Sweepstakes</h6>
<p>Drawings will be held randomly from all the online entered codes and codes entered via emails. These drawings will be separate for each of Sponsor&#8217;s 14 Divisions. (ACME, Eastern, Denver, Houston, Intermountain, Jewel-Osco, Northern California, Portland, Shaw’s, Seattle, Southwest, Southern California, and United) The drawings will be held on February 15, February 22, March 1, March 8, March 15, March 22, March 29, April 6, April 12, April 19, April 26, May 3, and May 10, 2017. Each winner from each division will receive a $1,000 grocery gift card.</p>
<p>Beside to above, in a bonus drawing, 1 winner from each division will be selected for the following prizes. February 22, 2017 – $5,000 Grocery Gift Card; March 7, 2017 – $10,000 Family Vacation Prize; April 26, 2017 – $20,000 College Tuition Prize; and June 2, 2017 – $40,000 Home Makeover Prize.</p>
<h6>How to Enter in Draw via Mail</h6>
<ul>
<li>Stick on your MONOPOLY Online Coupon Code to a 3&#8243; X 5&#8243; index card.</li>
<li>Write up your name, address, (including city, state and zip code), phone number, age and add your official signature on the card.</li>
<li>Now mail your entry by hand addressed the envelope to 2nd Chance Sweepstakes, P.O. Box 441208, Kennesaw, GA 30160.</li>
</ul>
<h6>Progressive Jackpot</h6>
<ul>
<li>100 Monopoly online coupon codes are eligible to win the Progressive Jackpot. The Progressive Jackpot amount will continue to increase on the website over the time.</li>
<li>The progressive jackpot will start at $1,000 and will continue to grow until the jackpot code is entered on the website and is won by someone. After which the amount will revert to $1,000 and then again starts to grow.</li>
</ul>
<h6>Hawaii&#8217;s Own Sweepstakes</h6>
<p>Each of the coupons entered online will automatically be submitted to a random drawing. The winner will get a chance to win one Hawaii Vacation.</p>
<h6>Last Chance Drawing</h6>
<p>If top 6 prizes will not be claimed by anyone up to 30, May 2017. ONLY THEN a random drawing will be conducted named as (LAST CHANCE DRAWING) in which all valid MONOPOLY 2nd chance sweepstakes entries occur on or about June 12, 2017, for one $1,000,000 Cash (30-year annuity) Prize.</p>
<h6>Nickelodeon Sweepstakes</h6>
<p>When anyone registers, and play Nickelodeon game then each coupon submitted will be entered into a random drawing. The participant will get a chance to win one of 3 Family Vacation for four to the Nickelodeon Resort in Punta Cana, Dominican Republic.</p>
<h5>Win Over $200 Million In Prizes And Money Saving Offers</h5>
<p>Game Board Prizes (1,753,271 Prizes; total ARV $24,005,000)</p>
<ul>
<li>(3) $1,000,000 Cash</li>
<li>(3) $1,000,000 Vacation Home</li>
<li>(15) $100,000 Cash or Luxury Car</li>
<li>(25) $40,000 Home Makeover</li>
<li>(25) $35,000 Vehicle of Your Choice</li>
<li>(50) $20,000 College Tuition</li>
<li>(50) $10,000 4-Wheeler</li>
<li>(50) $10,000 Family Vacation</li>
<li>(50) $5,000 Cash</li>
<li>(100) $1,500 Gas Grill &amp; Groceries</li>
<li>(100) $1,500 LED HD TV</li>
<li>(100) $1,000 Cash</li>
<li>(100) $1,000 Laptop Computer</li>
<li>(600) $300 Smart Watch</li>
<li>(50) $5,000 Groceries</li>
<li>(100) $1,000 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(350) $500 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(750) $200 Family Picnic</li>
<li>(2,500) $100 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(5,000) $50 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Gift Card Mall</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Fandango Gift Card</li>
<li>(25,000) $15 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(37,500) $10 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(800,000) $5 Grocery Gift Card</li>
<li>(750) $200 Cash</li>
<li>(2,500) $100 Cash</li>
<li>(10,000) $25 Cash</li>
<li>(37,500) $10 Cash</li>
<li>(800,000) $5 Cash</li>
</ul>
<h5>Instant Win Prizes (172,017,713 Prizes; total ARV $505,904,934)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(3) prizes of $10,000 Cash</li>
<li>(5) prizes of $5,000 Cash</li>
<li>(234,155) Grocery Gift Card prizes of $5,000, $1,000, $100, $50, $25, $10 and $5</li>
<li>(30,000) $25 Special Gift Card prizes from Burger King, MasterCard, Visa, Macy’s, GAP, JCPenney, Microsoft Xbox, AMC Theaters, Fandango, Nike and Regal Cinemas</li>
<li>(2,000) $20 Special Gift Card prizes from Domino’s</li>
<li>(14,000,000) prizes $24.99 Rouxbe Cooking School Class</li>
<li>(97,751,550) Free Product Prizes</li>
<li>(60,000,000) Two Free Game Tickets</li>
</ul>
<h5>Instant Discount Offers (58,350,000 Discounts, total ARV $681,802,500)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(9,000,000) $29.99 Shutterfly Photo Book</li>
<li>(4,750,000) $15.15 Shutterfly Prints</li>
<li>(9,750,000) $14.99 Shutterfly Shopping Bag</li>
<li>(4,750,000) $8.99 Shutterfly Magnet</li>
<li>(2,500,000) Let Life Bloom $10 e-gift certificates</li>
<li>(25,000,000) Let Life Bloom $5 e-gift certificates</li>
<li>(50,000) $10 off $100 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(75,000) $5 off $50 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(100,000) $2 off $20 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(2,375,000) Let Life Bloom Discounts of 15%</li>
</ul>
<h5>Online Game Prizes (325,338,010 Prizes; total ARV $36,959,250)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(10) $10,000 Cash Prizes</li>
<li>(38,000) Grocery Gift Card Prizes ranging from $25 to $1,000</li>
<li>(1,000,000) $24.99 Rouxbe Cooking School Class Prizes</li>
<li>(300,000) $21.99 Nickelodeon 40-pack Special Edition Oliver labels</li>
<li>(600,000) $5 Nickelodeon 12 count Special Edition Mini Oliver’s labels</li>
<li>(272,500,000) Fandango Reward Tokens</li>
<li>(180,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Dora’s Big Buddy Race through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Kate! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Pablo! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Naiya! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Emma! through Google Play</li>
<li>(144,000) 99¢ Nickelodeon Dora eBooks titled Meet Alana! through Google Play</li>
<li>(50,000,000) Two Free Game Tickets</li>
</ul>
<h5>Online Discount Offers (72,985,000 Discounts, total ARV: $56,590,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(1,000,000) $29.99 Shutterfly Photo Book discount offers</li>
<li>(5,000,000) Let Life Bloom $5 e-gift certificate</li>
<li>(20,000) $10 off $100 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(40,000) $5 off $50 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(100,000) $2 off $20 Purchase coupons</li>
<li>(1,000,000) General Mills Box Tops for Education</li>
<li>(40,000,000) Nickelodeon downloadable Activity Sheets</li>
<li>(24,000,000) Nickelodeon Digital Game Codes</li>
<li>(900,000) Nickelodeon TMNT (Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles) Digital Game Codes</li>
<li>(925,000) Nickelodeon Oliver’s Labels Discounts of 30%, 40% or 50%</li>
</ul>
<h5>Cents off Coupons (304,546,450 Coupons; total ARV: $182,423,324)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Cents off coupons ranging from 50¢ to $5 with 107 different coupons with an average of 59.9¢.</li>
</ul>
<h5>2nd Chance Sweepstakes (238 Prizes; total ARV: $1,232,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>(182) $1,000 Grocery Gift Card Prize</li>
<li>(14) $5,000 Grocery Gift Card Prize</li>
<li>(14) $10,000 Family Vacation Prize</li>
<li>(14) $20,000 College Tuition Prize</li>
<li>(14) $40,000 Home Makeover Prize</li>
</ul>
<h5>Nickelodeon Sweepstakes (3 Prizes; total ARV: $30,150)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Family Vacation for four (two adults and two children) to the Nickelodeon Resort in Punta Cana, Dominican Republic. This sweepstakes prize will include airfare, resort accommodations for four nights and $4,000 in cash.</li>
</ul>
<h5>Hawaii’s Own Sweepstakes (2 Prizes; total ARV: $14,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Hawaii Vacation for Two to the Waikiki Parc Hotel in Honolulu, Hawaii. This sweepstakes prize will include airfare, resort accommodations for five nights and $2,500 in cash.</li>
</ul>
<h5>Progressive Jackpot (100 Prizes; total ARV: $250,000)</h5>
<ul>
<li>Progressive Jackpot prizes begin at $1,000 with a maximum total value of $250,000.</li>
</ul>
<h5>Last Chance Drawing</h5>
<ul>
<li>(1) $1,000,000 Cash (30-year annuity) Prize</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/">Monopoly Game At Safeway: Shop &#038; Get a Chance to Win $200 Million</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-playmonopoly-us-monopoly-game-at-safeway/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>www.auburntigers.com &#8211; Get Latest Updates on Your Favorite Team of AUBURN Football</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-auburntigers-com/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-auburntigers-com/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3509</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Check out the latest details about Auburn football team players, stats, and rosters by visiting www.auburntigers.com. ‘Whoever invented football should be worshiped as a God’Said Hugo Sanche &#8216;a former Mexican footballer.&#8221; You are a football fan and you are watching a mind blowing match between the toughest of the teams. You are practically glued to [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-auburntigers-com/">www.auburntigers.com &#8211; Get Latest Updates on Your Favorite Team of AUBURN Football</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Check out the latest details about Auburn football team players, stats, and rosters by visiting <a href="http://www.auburntigers.com/">www.auburntigers.com</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="modern-quote full"><p>‘Whoever invented football should be worshiped as a God’<cite>Said Hugo Sanche &#8216;a former Mexican footballer.&#8221;</cite></p></blockquote>
<p>You are a football fan and you are watching a mind blowing match between the toughest of the teams.</p>
<p>You are <strong>practically glued to the screen</strong>, and no amount of commotion in your vicinity can be your attention. It’s like you are out there in the field, as a matter of fact, emotionally you are there. You are overwhelmed with excitement, you can feel the adrenaline rushing through your blood and nothing on this entire planet is more important than the battle raging out there. You can relate to this, right? Well, most of us can. <strong>Football is filled with thrill</strong>, enthusiasm, ending sometimes in glorious triumphs and sometimes in depressing defeats.</p>
<p>Either way, it gives you an emotional surge that alone is bound to make you feel infatuated with it. This is what all above things you can get on <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">www.auburntigers.com</span></em>. Auburn University official site provides you much information about the players and upcoming matches. You can enjoy the upcoming events at the website <span style="color: #808080;"><em>www.auburntigers.com</em></span></p>
<p>Either way, it gives you an emotional surge that alone is bound to make you feel infatuated with it. So, if you are a <strong>football fanatic</strong> and happen to live in Auburn, Alabama, you might want to get the latest updates on Auburn Football teams. <a href="http://www.al.com/auburnfootball/"><span style="text-decoration: underline;">www.al.com/auburnfootball/</span></a> brings you all the important stuff related to Auburn Tigers Team. You can also check out the recent football events and participate in active football discussions.</p>
<h2>www.auburntigers.com &#8211; TIGER FANS TALKS</h2>
<p>Nothing compares to the pleasure that comes with having someone to share an obsession with. Your football passion is by no means an exception; you feel connected by an ethereal relationship to all the people connected with football, be it other fans or players. So it’s time to <strong>share your football passion</strong> with millions of fans across the globe. Pour out all you feel about your favorite team, contribute to their betterment by pointing out the loop holes in the strategies or appreciate them for the good work they showed in the field. Here is how you can get started right away:</p>
<p>So it’s time to share your football passion with millions of fans across the globe. Pour out all you feel about your favorite team, <strong>contribute to their betterment</strong> by pointing out the loopholes in the strategies or appreciate them for the good work they showed in the field. Here is how you can get started right away:</p>
<ul>
<li>Just click on ‘<strong>Tiger Fans Talks</strong>’.</li>
<li>Type out your comments</li>
<li>Give a title to your post if you want. A title helps make your post stand out so that more and more people can participate in the discussion.</li>
<li>If you <strong>want to follow your post regularly</strong>, you need to create an account on al.com. Once you have an account you just have to log in to view the recent comments on your post.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Post</h3>
<p>Who will lead Auburn Defense in 2017? Will Auburn’s Tony Stevens make an NFL roster? How Auburn’s players tested at the Tigers’ Pro Day? If these <strong>questions are rolling in your mind</strong> and you are looking for reliable answers, then there is no better place than <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">www.al.com</span></em> to find them. Read all the new stories form Auburns Tigers in the Top Posts.</p>
<h3>SCHEDULE, STANDINGS AND PLAYERS</h3>
<p>This is where you can find the more specific details of all the tournaments and games. The Schedule section features <strong>all the upcoming matches</strong> along with the names of rival teams. In the Standings section you get to know how good the ranking of Auburn Football team is amongst the other teams. The detailed information of the scores is also given here. ‘The Players’ of course, has the names of all those part of the team along with their roles. For example, S. White is responsible for passing yards and TDs.</p>
<h3>AUBURN TIGERS TODAY</h3>
<p>Want to get the latest news from Auburn Tigers delivered right to your inbox?</p>
<ul>
<li>Go to <a href="http://www.auburntigers.com/">www.auburntigers.com</a>.</li>
<li>Scroll down</li>
<li>Enter your email address in the dialog box named ‘Auburn Tigers Today’</li>
<li>Hit the ‘Subscribe’ button</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-auburntigers-com/">www.auburntigers.com &#8211; Get Latest Updates on Your Favorite Team of AUBURN Football</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-auburntigers-com/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anderson Cooper 360 Review &#8211; Going Beyond the Headlines</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/anderson-cooper-360/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/anderson-cooper-360/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 18:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3507</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to hear the latest news on Trump’s new policies? Need a comprehensive analysis of the everyday political events? Anderson Cooper 360 review brings you the hottest news of the day from multiple viewpoints. So you not only get in-depth coverage but also the other side of the story enabling you to form your own [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/anderson-cooper-360/">Anderson Cooper 360 Review &#8211; Going Beyond the Headlines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to hear the latest news on Trump’s new policies? Need a <strong><span style="color: #808080;"><em>comprehensive analysis of the everyday political events</em></span></strong>? <strong>Anderson Cooper 360 review</strong> brings you the hottest news of the day from multiple viewpoints. So you not only get in-depth coverage but also the other side of the story enabling you to form your own opinion on the matter.</p>
<p>It is markedly different from the conventional talk shows where you are forced to listen to heated arguments and still not have a sound knowledge of the real issue. <strong>Anderson really goes beyond the headlines</strong> clearly delineating the current affairs into points that even the layman can understand, not just the experts of analysis. The show AC360 is aired at 8 pm ET and is repeated at 10 pm ET on CNN on all the weeknights.</p>
<p>If you are looking for a comprehensive and coherent analysis of the current news across the globe, tune in to Anderson Cooper 360 every day at 8 pm ET. You can access videos and other content of the show at <a href="http://edition.cnn.com/shows/ac-360/">edition.cnn.com/shows/ac-360/</a></p>
<h3>Anderson Cooper 360 &#8211; Segments of Show</h3>
<p>The show comprises of following segments:</p>
<ul>
<li>AC360</li>
<li>True politics</li>
<li>Keeping them honest</li>
<li>Crime and punishment</li>
<li>The Ridiculist</li>
<li>American Journey</li>
</ul>
<h3>AC360 BLOGS</h3>
<p>The brand new blog of AC 360 is your hub to all the new stories. Here you can not only watch all the latest shows but also sneak into the behind the camera stories. AC360 blog also features the <strong>extended versions of some of the biggest</strong> and the most influential discussions and interviews of Anderson Cooper. View the blog page of Anderson Cooper 360 at <a href="http://ac360.blogs.cnn.com/">ac360.blogs.cnn.com</a></p>
<h3>ABOUT AC360</h3>
<p>AC360 is markedly different from the typical evening TV casts. Its <strong>unique content combines</strong> with the light humor of Anderson Cooper is refreshing and entertaining unlike the crude and boring style of the most talk shows.</p>
<p>AC360 won two Emmy Awards in 2011 for their extensive coverage of the earthquake in Haiti. It also received Emmy Awards in 2006 for outstanding coverage of the famine in Nigeria and for a feature story on a Charity Hospital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/anderson-cooper-360/">Anderson Cooper 360 Review &#8211; Going Beyond the Headlines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/anderson-cooper-360/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>www.barbie.com &#8216;LIFE IN THE DREAMHOUSE&#8217; Watch all New Episodes</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-barbie-com/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-barbie-com/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 10:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3504</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Even after the passage of 55 years since its debut in 1959, Barbie still continues to inspire young girls all over the world with her fantasy roles and careers by visiting www.barbie.com. The Barbie concept was not received with much favor initially owing to a possibility of harming the self-esteem of young girls, but despite [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-barbie-com/">www.barbie.com &#8216;LIFE IN THE DREAMHOUSE&#8217; Watch all New Episodes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even after the passage of 55 years since its debut in 1959, <strong>Barbie still continues to inspire young girls</strong> all over the world with her fantasy roles and careers by visiting <span style="color: #808080;"><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>www.barbie.com</strong></span></em></span>. The Barbie concept was not received with much favor initially owing to a possibility of harming the self-esteem of young girls, but despite those skepticism, Barbie tales have a long history of evoking confidence and motivation among preteen girls.</p>
<blockquote class="modern-quote full"><p>My whole philosophy of Barbie was that, through the doll little girl could be anything she wanted to be. Barbie always represented the fact that a woman has choices.<cite>Ruth Handler &#8211; &#8220;creator of the Barbie doll.&#8221;</cite></p></blockquote>
<p>Many Barbie stories have powerful lessons hidden in them, which can be easily accessed by visiting <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><a href="http://www.barbie.com/">www.barbie.com</a></span></em> which may lead to a positive behavioral change in kids. If you are a kid of 90s, the odds are that you too have a strong emotional association with those Barbie dolls and stories. No matter how much grown up you are now; you can <strong>ascribe hundreds of sw</strong><strong style="font-size: 14px;">eet memories</strong><span style="font-size: 14px;"> to Barbie alone. So why not breathe through your childhood a bit?</span></p>
<p>‘Barbie: Life in the dream house’ is an animated web series featuring the fictional franchise of Mattel, the Barbie. The first season of the series aired on the official website on May 11, 2012, and up to date, seven seasons have been released. A new episode comes every week when the new season is airing.</p>
<p>The main character of the series is, of course, Barbie, who lives in an exquisite mansion called the ‘Dreamhouse’ with her three little sisters <strong>Skipper</strong>, <strong>Stacie</strong>, and <strong>Chelsea</strong>. Barbie’s handsome boyfriend Ken is also an all-time favorite with the fans of the series. He stands by Barbie, no matter what happens.</p>
<h2>www.barbie.com &#8211; Watch all New Episodes of LIFE IN THE DREAMHOUSE</h2>
<p>The show is more like a reality show featuring the everyday adventures of Barbie and her friends. If you are looking for a show that is not only entertaining but also dramatic and thrilling, you might want to check out <strong>‘</strong><em><strong>Barbie: Life in the Dreamhouse</strong></em><strong>’</strong>. To <strong>Watch the current and previous seasons</strong> of the show, go to <a href="http://www.barbie.com/dreamhouse">www.barbie.com/dreamhouse</a>.</p>
<p>Here are some of the exciting things that you can do by logging on to the website:</p>
<h3>New Episode</h3>
<p>Watch the latest episodes of the current season every Wednesday. Just click on the ‘Episodes’ icon on the top of the web page and <strong><span style="color: #808080;"><em>delve into the world of Barbie</em></span></strong>.</p>
<h3>Games</h3>
<p>Looking for some good games? Well, why not check out some really interesting ones at ‘Life in the dream house’? <span style="color: #3366ff;"><em>Great Puppy Treasure Hunt</em></span>, <em><span style="color: #3366ff;">Barbie Dreamtopia Adventure Games</span></em>, <span style="color: #3366ff;"><em>Starlight adventure</em></span>, and many other amazing games are bound to keep you glued to the screen for hours.</p>
<h3>Cast and Crew</h3>
<p>Want to know more about your favorite dolls in ‘<span style="color: #808080;"><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Life in the Dream House</span></em></span>’. Just click on the ‘cast’ button and you’ll get to know everything about all the characters in the show.</p>
<h3>Maps</h3>
<p>Isn’t the dream house incredible? Would you love to see it from the inside? Sadly your wish cannot be fulfilled given that this is all fiction. But you can virtually walk through the doors of the dream house. Just click on the ‘<strong>Maps</strong>’ section and feel like you are there.</p>
<p>This feature also lets you take a detailed tour through the city of Malibu where the series is set. This is actually the fictitious doll-sized version of the original city.</p>
<h3>Shop</h3>
<p>This is where you can buy some really cool Barbie stuff. You can get video games, toys, play sets and a lot more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-barbie-com/">www.barbie.com &#8216;LIFE IN THE DREAMHOUSE&#8217; Watch all New Episodes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-barbie-com/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>www.BassMaster.com &#8211; Join Bass Anglers Sportsman Society For Fishing Tips &#038; News</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-bassmaster-com/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-bassmaster-com/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 17:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3470</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Sounds strange, eh? It might if you are content with just the tuna fish roll and have never experienced fishing as a sports, so you can visit www.BassMaster.com for more details. Ask anyone who has gone fishing and they can ascertain that it is fun no matter how pathetic you are at the actual game. [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-bassmaster-com/">www.BassMaster.com &#8211; Join Bass Anglers Sportsman Society For Fishing Tips &#038; News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sounds strange, eh? It might if you are content with just the tuna fish roll and have never experienced fishing as a sports, so you can visit <span style="color: #0000ff;"><strong><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">www.BassMaster.com</span></em></strong></span> for more details. <strong>Ask anyone who has gone fishing</strong> and they can ascertain that it is fun no matter how pathetic you are at the actual game.</p>
<p>It’s a perfect way of taking a break from the strains of your sporadic routine and of having some really quiet moments to rewind your life and reflect on the past. While it may seem a quiet sport, it is fraught with excitement and adventure. The rush and the thrill you feel when you are after a wild fish is in itself a great reward of engaging in this sport. <strong>A UNIFIED VOICE OF BASS FISHERMEN</strong></p>
<blockquote class="modern-quote full"><p>‘There is more to catching fish than just fish’</p></blockquote>
<p>If you want to enjoy fishing to the fullest and be part of the most accomplished angler community log on to <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.bassmaster.com</em></span> and get ready to dive into the world of bass fishing. <strong>Bassmaster is the place</strong> where anglers from all over the globe share their passion for bass fishing and participate in exciting tournaments.</p>
<p>The Bassmaster Tournament Trail and the Bassmaster Classic are recognized as world’s <strong>leading fishing championships and thousands of people</strong> make their way to the coliseums to watch the game. Bassmaster is also the pioneer of the ethics of ‘Catch and Release.’ Now the majority of the bass anglers practice it in the world and of many other environment conservation programs.</p>
<h3>www.BassMaster.com &#8211; TIPS FOR BEGINNERS</h3>
<p>Are you new to fishing? No clue where to start? Need to start from the scratch? Bassmaster has it all you need to know about the Bass fishing. Just go to <strong>‘Tips’ section</strong> and check out brilliant videos on every aspect of the sports such as understanding the current, tying the knot, choosing the right line, spinnerbait selection and a lot more.</p>
<h3>BassMaster Membership</h3>
<p>BASS MASTER membership allows for a more exhilarating angling experience. Just go to <strong>‘Join’ icon at the top of the home page</strong>, click ‘Join B.A.S.S’, a new page appears where you can choose from the following membership programs:</p>
<ul>
<li>1 year membership for $15</li>
<li>3 year membership for $65</li>
<li>5 year membership for $100</li>
<li>LIFE membership for $450</li>
</ul>
<p>The benefits of Bassmaster membership include Bassmaster magazine, membership kit, <strong>automatic entry into monthly prizes</strong>, exclusive member discounts, and special offers from Bassmaster. You also receive free gifts when you join Bassmaster which include B.A.S.S Tackle Bag, B.A.S.S Logo Cap, Bassmaster Tips Books and an Ultimate Techniques DVD.</p>
<h4>Tournaments</h4>
<p>Never miss out on your favorite Bassmaster tournament; check out the schedules and details for all the Open, Elite and Classic championships in the Tournaments section.</p>
<h4>Get Bass Times</h4>
<p>Subscribe for BASS TIMES by filling out a simple form and get 50% off the retail rate on your favorite magazine. <strong>The BASS TIMES features</strong> some amazing content on BASS biology, detailed coverage of BASSMASTER tournaments and handy tips and techniques to maximize your catch.</p>
<h4>Get  A Chance to Fish With Gerald Swindle</h4>
<p>Want to fish with the 2016 Bassmaster Angler of the year ‘Gerald Swindle’ and a chance to <strong>win a prize worth $32,500?</strong> Here it is: just enter in to the sweepstakes by filling out a form available on the web page. You must have practiced bass fishing for the last two years to be eligible for entry. Even the non-member folks can apply without paying any additional charges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-bassmaster-com/">www.BassMaster.com &#8211; Join Bass Anglers Sportsman Society For Fishing Tips &#038; News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-bassmaster-com/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Visit AR15.com to Join The World’s Largest FireArm Community</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/ar15-com/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/ar15-com/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 17:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3469</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the normal belief, firearms are not inherently evil and for many people can visit AR15.com, they serve as an immensely gratifying hobby. Usually, people tend to look upon them as a means of violence but the odds are that most of them wouldn’t even know somebody who would go about threatening people with [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/ar15-com/">Visit AR15.com to Join The World’s Largest FireArm Community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the normal belief, firearms are not inherently evil and for many people can visit <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em><a style="color: #0000ff;" href="http://AR15.com/">AR15.com</a></em></span>, they serve as an immensely gratifying hobby. Usually, <strong>people tend to look upon them as a means of violence</strong> but the odds are that most of them wouldn’t even know somebody who would go about threatening people with guns and bombarding them with bullets. The <strong>gun enthusiasts</strong> have a wholly different outlook; they cherish the rush and thrill of target shooting, the terrific roar of a rifle shoot, the feel of the glistening gun in their hands.</p>
<p>The gun enthusiasts have a wholly different outlook; they cherish the rush and thrill of target shooting, the terrific roar of a rifle shoot, the feel of the glistening gun in their hands, in short they enjoy every aspect of this unique sport.</p>
<h2>AR15.com &#8211; Method for Joining FireArm Community</h2>
<p>Former senator Phil Gramm of Texas once said, ‘I own more shotguns than I need but not as many as I want,’ perfectly representing a typical firearm lover. Most of them are obsessed with hoarding the best equipments for feeding their passion and whether they do it for <strong>hunting, target shooting or simply for the sake of building a huge collection,</strong> they cannot stress enough the importance of a database where not only you can find the latest firearm equipment but also many valuable links to training and gear resources.</p>
<p>This is where <a href="http://www.ar15.com/">www.ar15.com</a>  comes in; being the world’s largest firearm community, it is your gateway to everything related to firearms. Furthermore, it came into being in 1996 primarily as a website to provide means to gun enthusiast to collect, explore and share information regarding firearms. Since then it has grown tremendously and the<em><strong> focus of the website</strong></em> is now shifted more towards the <em><strong>protection of firearm freedom</strong></em> and promotion of firearm sports.</p>
<p><span style="color: #808080;"><strong><em>AR15.com</em></strong></span> has free discussions forums and comment panels where you can gain in-depth information of all the modern gear and equipment. You can find more about AR15, AK47, precision rifles, handgun, armory, archery and even <strong>brilliant recommendations about different training</strong> such as Handgun training, Tactical Rifle training, Precision Rifle Training, and self-defense. You can even engage in conversation with the people bringing you the dependable and versatile firearms and know more about their equipment.</p>
<p>The website also provides easily accessible links to all the leading firearm brands and retailers so you can enjoy the <strong>best gun gear available.</strong> These include Capitol Armory, Faxon Barrels, Geissele AUTOMATICS, Primary Arms, BROWNELLS, FORTIS, BCM and many other top notch firearm manufacturers.</p>
<h3>REGISTER AT AR15.COM</h3>
<p>Gear up to share your passion with over 300,000 firearm enthusiasts from all across the world. You need to fill out a simple registration form to create a free account at ar15.com. Just click on ‘Register’ icon on the top of the home page, provide your initials, email address, country, state and gain access to the best firearm resources at <a href="http://www.ar15.com/">www.ar15.com</a>. Due to security issues, only company or ISP email accounts will be acceptable for registration.</p>
<h4>AR15.COM TEAM MEMBERSHIPS</h4>
<p>To gain access to unlimited current and archived data regarding firearms and to enjoy a more customized version of the website, become an <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">AR15.com</span></em> Team Member. There are three different membership options:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Bronze Membership worth $24</strong></li>
<li><strong>Gold Membership worth $60</strong></li>
<li><strong>Platinum Membership worth $100</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>All the memberships are for a period of twelve months and do not automatically renew. Moreover, they offer diverse benefits including enhanced search ability, special site resources, Avatar and Team Member Title, increased media storage, team member giveaways and a lot more that you can check out at <a href="http://www.ar15.com/about/memberships.html">www.ar15.com/about/memberships.html</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/ar15-com/">Visit AR15.com to Join The World’s Largest FireArm Community</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/ar15-com/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Now Watch AMC Live at Amc.com</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/amc-com-amc-live/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/amc-com-amc-live/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 16:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3468</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you a fan of hair-raising and nail-biting thrillers? Then you must subscribe for AMC Live at AMC.com do you love the squirmy feeling in your stomach you get when you watch your favorite show and can’t wait to know what happens next? Looking forward to a roller coaster ride of pure entertainment and thrill? [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/amc-com-amc-live/">Now Watch AMC Live at Amc.com</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you a fan of hair-raising and nail-biting thrillers? Then you must subscribe for <strong>AMC Live</strong> at <a href="http://AMC.com/">AMC.com</a> do you love the <strong>squirmy feeling</strong> in your stomach you get when you watch your favorite show and can’t wait to know what happens next?</p>
<p>Looking forward to a roller coaster ride of pure entertainment and thrill? AMC is here to <strong>quench your thirst with some of the most exhilarating and fantastic shows</strong> on TV including the Walking Dead, HUMANS, The Son, Comic Book Man, Mad Men, Into the Badlands, The Night Manager, Halt and Catch Fire, and a lot more.</p>
<h2>AMC Live at Your TV</h2>
<p>The recent episodes of all the in-season serials are easily available on <a href="http://www.amc.com/">www.amc.com</a>  but a day after the premiere on AMC. If you want to see the on-air content, your TV provider must provide access to AMC Channel.</p>
<p><em><strong>Following TV providers in the United States offer access to AMC live service currently:</strong></em></p>
<ul>
<li>AT&amp;T U-verse</li>
<li>Spectrum</li>
<li>Charter</li>
<li>Xfinity</li>
<li>DIRECTV</li>
<li>DISH</li>
<li>OPTIMUM</li>
</ul>
<p>If you don’t see your TV provider in the list above don’t lose heart since this list is being continuously updated so yours might be just there in a while.</p>
<h3>AMC Live</h3>
<p>All the <strong>on-air content of AMC</strong> is available for live streaming at <a href="http://amc.com/">amc.com</a> for viewers whose TV providers offer access to AMC channel. Users are usually required to provide their TV ID to watch AMC Live however at times promotional episodes are available for all the viewers regardless of their subscription status.</p>
<p>Once you <em><strong>log in with your TV subscription ID and password,</strong></em> you can sign up for amc.com account and enjoy the following exclusive benefits</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Receive new episode reminders</strong></li>
<li><strong>Resume your episode</strong></li>
<li><strong>Share your views with other fans</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Having an <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">amc.com</span></em> account is not mandatory to watch your favorite content but who doesn’t want to have a more customized version of AMC LIVE?</p>
<h3>AMC Live Stream Supported Browser</h3>
<p>For both Windows and Mac Os users, the <strong>recommended browsers</strong> are Internet Explorer 9 or a higher version, Firefox, Google, and Safari. The website is mobile friendly so you can enjoy all the features ofamc.com also on your smartphone.</p>
<h3>Schedule</h3>
<p>To check for the timings of your favorite show, enter the full title of the show into <strong>SEARCH FULL SCHEDULE</strong> box. If the show is to be aired within two weeks, both the date and time will immediately show up. If you do know what channel is AMC in your area, just click on the ‘Schedule’ section at the bottom of the home page, go to AMC channel finder, enter your ZIP code and there you are.</p>
<h3>Newsletter Subscription</h3>
<p>Don’t want to miss out anything on your favorite TV shows? AMC makes sure that you really don’t, <strong>no matter how busy your schedule is</strong>. Just go to the bottom of the home page and click ‘Newsletter’. A new page appears where you need to enter your email address and select the shows whose updates you want to receive. You will also gain early access to exclusive photos, news and videos with the newsletter subscription.</p>
<h3>Shop With AMC</h3>
<p>Really obsessed with The Walking Dead? Want to have a <strong>logo T-shirt or hoodie</strong>? Visit the AMC Shop page and get exclusive stuff in terms of clothing, accessories, collectibles, games, costumes and books. You can also buy your favorite series DVD or Blue Ray.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/amc-com-amc-live/">Now Watch AMC Live at Amc.com</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/amc-com-amc-live/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
