<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Shopping &#8211; TheFinancials</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thefinancials.net/shopping/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 17:50:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What is Inventory Turnover Ratio</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/inventory-turnover-ratio/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/inventory-turnover-ratio/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thefinancials.net/?p=4576</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Inventory Turnover Ratio = (Sales ÷ Inventory) Inventory Turnover Ratio tells the analyst about how quickly a company is converting its inventory in to sales. This ratio gives a deep look into the inventory management skills of a company. Where you can view the capability of retaining inventory and making sales. In addition to above [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/inventory-turnover-ratio/">What is Inventory Turnover Ratio</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Inventory Turnover Ratio = (Sales ÷ Inventory)</strong></p>
<p>Inventory Turnover Ratio tells the analyst about how quickly a company is converting its inventory in to sales. This ratio gives a deep look into the inventory management skills of a company. Where you can view the capability of retaining inventory and making sales. In addition to above it can help you to reconsider the inventory holding policies for cost cutting.</p>
<p>To calculate Inventory Turnover ratio you can use &#8216;average inventory&#8217; in the denominator. If you are using monthly sales in numerator then you must have to use average inventory of that month.</p>
<p>Inventory turnover ratio formula do not take account of fixed expenses. Moreover, it do not consider the cost of goods sold or any other debt involved in manufacturing process. But on the other hand cost of goods sold only focuses on certain variable expenses and do not account for other fixed costs.</p>
<p>For example: If a company sales are going lower and in turn decides to lower inventory for maintaining turnover ratio. But company may not be able to maintain the burden of debt with lower sales volume.</p>
<p>So, it is established thing that inventory turnover ratio only gives a limited view of a business. Moreover, it cannot replace liquidity ratio i.e. current ratio and it only serves a certain purpose in analysis.</p>
<h2>Alternative to Standard Inventory Turnover Formula</h2>
<p>There is also an alternative to standard inventory turnover ratio. Both are considered fine however, people use them respectively in different scenarios.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Inventory Turnover = (Cost of goods sold ÷ Inventory)</strong></p>
<p>As it is apparent that this approach uses <span style="text-decoration: underline;">cost of goods sold</span> method and it depicts the ability of a company to meet direct cost of selling products. As it do not take in to account the overall cost of business operations. It is worth saying that this approach is very helpful when comparing two companies.</p>
<p>Lets say, Company A and Company B are in same industry however, Company B has a higher gross profit. Both sell 5,000 units and cost of goods sold is same in both companies. However, Company B selling price is slightly higher than company A. If you calculate Inventory turnover ratio with SALES in numerator the ratio will be same. However Company B will have a lower turnover ratio if you use COGS in numerator.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/inventory-turnover-ratio/">What is Inventory Turnover Ratio</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/inventory-turnover-ratio/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bags2Riches.com: A Contest By Price Chopper To Win $1,000,000</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/bags2riches-com-price-chopper-promotion/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/bags2riches-com-price-chopper-promotion/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 22:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.theguidance.info/?p=4505</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Bags2Riches is a Game by Price Chopper for 2018, Visit Bags2Riches.com to take part in the promotion. Get a chance to win $1,000,000 in cash for the first grand prize winner. There are many other prizes also including, 1 in 3 tickets for great food or discounts. Moreover, winners will also get a chance to [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/bags2riches-com-price-chopper-promotion/">Bags2Riches.com: A Contest By Price Chopper To Win $1,000,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bags2Riches</strong> is a Game by Price Chopper for 2018, Visit <span style="color: #0000ff;">Bags2Riches.com</span> to take part in the promotion. Get a chance to win $1,000,000 in cash for the first grand prize winner. There are many other prizes also including, 1 in 3 tickets for great food or discounts. Moreover, winners will also get a chance to win a car, free gas for a whole year, and many more things.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-4507" src="https://www.theguidance.info/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Bags2Riches.jpg" alt="Bags2Riches.com" width="695" height="358" srcset="https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Bags2Riches.jpg 695w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Bags2Riches-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.thefinancials.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/Bags2Riches-300x155@2x.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></p>
<p>The total amount of $6 million is available in terms of prizes and discounts to be won by participants. This amount also includes $1 million of the grand prize. To increase the chances of winning the game, you have to play more. <span style="color: #0000ff;"><a style="color: #0000ff;" href="http://www.bags2riches.com/">Play Here</a></span></p>
<h2>Bags2Riches.com &#8211; How to Participate in Contest</h2>
<p>In order to participate in the contest, you will need to get Bags2Riches game tickets. This contest is for Bags2Riches 2018 period.</p>
<ul>
<li>Participant has to <strong>spend at least</strong> $25 by using AdvantEdge card at any outlet of Price Chopper or Market Bistro which is taking part in a contest to get 1 game ticket.</li>
<li>Purchases of $50 to get 2 game tickets.</li>
<li>Purchases of $75 to get 3 game tickets.</li>
<li>Max. limit of tickets is 12 in one shopping trip.</li>
</ul>
<p>Another way to get a <strong>ticket is via email</strong>, you can simply request a Bags2Riches ticket in an email. Just write up your full name, mailing address, AdvantEdge card number, email address and phone number on a card of 3&#8243; X 5&#8243;. The card must also contain some lines about your likings about the Price Chopper store. You can then send the envelope to;</p>
<p><span style="color: #999999;"><em>Price Chopper Bags2Riches Number purchase Tickets, P.O. Box 783, Tonawanda NY, 14151-0783.</em></span></p>
<p><em>The limit for mailing is up to 12 Tickets per request, per day, one request per outer mailing envelope.</em></p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>How to Play Bags2Riches Game</h3>
<p>There are about 4 different ways to play the game and be a participant in this promotion by Price Chopper.</p>
<p><strong>&#8211; Instant Win:</strong> One in three-game tickets to get a food prize or discount on it. If your ticket shows a message &#8220;<strong>You Win</strong>&#8221; or Save &#8220;<strong>$1.00 off</strong>&#8221; then you will get an instant Win prize or instant Discount. There are about 5,466,715 instant win prizes or discounts available for participants during the entire promotion period.</p>
<p><strong>&#8211; Collect to Win:</strong> All game tickets will contain 3 collect to win stickers. You have to match stickers to complete any of 11 categories from the collector card. In return, you <strong>can win $1,000,000 cash</strong>, new Cadillac XT5 SUV, Kitchen Makeover, luxury Cruise, free gas for a year, free groceries for a year, and much more.<br />
If there are any duplicate stickers, then there is no issue. Just clip them up and complete the entry form and mail to Price Chopper <span style="color: #0000ff;">Bags2Riches.com</span> address as below.<br />
<span style="color: #999999;"><em>P.O. Box 784 Tonawanda NY 14151-0784 to participate in a chance to win $5,000.</em></span></p>
<p><strong>&#8211; Online Sweepstakes:</strong> If you get a <em>9-digit code</em> printed on the ticket, then visit Bags2Riches.com and fill up the registration form. Don&#8217;t forget to enter your pin, enroll today to get a chance to win $10,000 cash, Price Chopper gift cards, Free Gas for a year and much more.</p>
<h4>Instant Win Prizes</h4>
<p>&#8211; $10,000 Cash each for 5 Winners<br />
&#8211; $1,000 Cash each for 1,000 Winners<br />
&#8211; Free gas for a year &#8211; each for 25 Winners<br />
&#8211; $50 Price Chopper gift cards each for 1,000 Winners<br />
&#8211; And much more</p>
<h4>Collect to Win Prizes</h4>
<ul>
<li><strong>1,000,000 &#8211; Grand Prize</strong> &amp; 1 Winner Only. Collect stickers from A301, A302, A303, A304, A305, A306, A307, A308, A309, A310, A311 and A312</li>
<li>2017 Cadillac XT5 or $50,000 &#8211; Each for 3 winnersCollect stickers from B313, B314, B315, B316, B317, B318, B319, B320, B321 and B322.</li>
<li>$25,000 Kitchen Makeover &#8211; Each for 5 winners. Collect stickers from C323, C324, C325, C326, C327, C328, C329 and C330.</li>
<li>$10,000 Luxury Cruise OR $10,000 Cash &#8211; Each for 5 winners. Collect stickers from D331, D332, D333, D334, D335, D336, D337 and D338.</li>
<li>Free Groceries for a Year &#8211; Each for 25 winners. Collect stickers from E339, E340, E341, E342, E343 and E344.</li>
<li>Free Gas for a Year &#8211; Each for 50 winners. Collect stickers from F345, F346, F347, F348, F349 and F350.</li>
<li>$250 Price Chopper Gift Card &#8211; Each for 750 Winners. Collect stickers from G351, G352, G353, G354, and G355.</li>
<li>$50 Price Chopper Gift Card &#8211; Each for 2,000 Winners. Collect stickers from H356, H357, H358, H359, and H360.</li>
<li>The three guaranteed double up sweepstakes winners will receive one of the following prizes;</li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li>$5,000 Cash</li>
<li>$5,000 in Sunoco Gift Cards</li>
<li>Vacation Getaway of worth $5,000</li>
</ol>
<h4>Online Sweepstakes Prize</h4>
<p>This category winner will get one of the following prizes.</p>
<ol>
<li>$100 Price Chopper gift card &#8211; Each for 78 winners.</li>
<li>Free gas for a year &#8211; Each for 10 winners.</li>
<li>Grand Prize $10,000 Cash &#8211; 1 winner only.</li>
<li>Early Brid &#8211; $10,000 Luxury Hot Tub / Home Spa &#8211; 1 Winner only</li>
</ol>
<h3>Important to Know Before Playing Bags2Riches Game</h3>
<ul>
<li>This <strong>promotion is only open</strong> to residents of CT, NH, MA, NY, NJ, PA, RI or VT and over the age of majority.</li>
<li>You can get tickets from 137 Price Chopper, Market Bistro, and Market 32 outlets.</li>
<li>The <strong>game period</strong> is of about 3 months starting from 15 January and ending on March 25. If the tickets supply finishes before this, then promotion will be considered ended.</li>
<li>The total value of prizes and discounts is approx. $6,271,727.20</li>
<li>This promotion is sponsored by Golub Corporation, Schenectady, New York, USA, 12308-1058.</li>
<li>Moreover, this promotion is administrated by WSP International Limited, Markham Ontario, Canada, L3R 1H5.</li>
</ul>
<p>To get more info about the Price Chopper Bags2Riches <a href="https://www.bags2riches.com/module/Bags2riches2017/doc/rules.pdf">Game rules</a> visits <span style="color: #0000ff;"><a style="color: #0000ff;" href="http://www.bags2riches.com/">www.bags2riches.com</a></span> for details.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/bags2riches-com-price-chopper-promotion/">Bags2Riches.com: A Contest By Price Chopper To Win $1,000,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/bags2riches-com-price-chopper-promotion/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Submit an Asurion Phone Claim</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-phoneclaim-com-asurion-phone-claim/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-phoneclaim-com-asurion-phone-claim/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 14:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3325</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Go to www.phoneclaim.com and submit your Asurion phone claim using the Asurion phone protection plan if your phone is lost, stolen or broken. If you have lost your phone or it is stolen then you can submit an Asurion phone claim. But one is only eligible for this if he/she has bought wireless phone protection [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-phoneclaim-com-asurion-phone-claim/">How to Submit an Asurion Phone Claim</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Go to <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.phoneclaim.com</em></span> and submit your <em><strong>Asurion phone claim</strong></em> using the Asurion phone protection plan if your phone is lost, stolen or broken. If you have lost your phone or it is stolen then you can submit an Asurion phone claim. But one is only eligible for this if he/she has bought wireless phone protection with Asurion. The person will get the replacement phone in a short period of time after the approval of claim at Asurion.</p>
<h2>www.phoneclaim.com Protection Works?</h2>
<p>Asurion is an insurance agency and provides technology protection services to its customers. Besides to that, it also offers insurance coverage for your wireless devices. Asurion offers easy, fast and convenient services to its customers.</p>
<p>If your phone is lost, stolen or even it is broken then you will get a replacement of your phone after you submit your Asurion Phone Claim. The new phone will reach within 60-days right after you qualify for it.</p>
<h3>How to Submit an Asurion Phone Claim?</h3>
<h6 style="padding-left: 30px;">Pre-Requisites</h6>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">To qualify for the service, you must also buy the Asurion Wireless Phone Protection plan with your phone. Right before you start using the phone moreover, you must have a phone number.</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;">File up the claim, within 60-days of the incident (lost, stolen or broken).</p>
<h6 style="padding-left: 30px;">Steps to Submit Claim</h6>
<ol>
<li style="padding-left: 30px;">Visit the <strong><a href="http://www.phoneclaim.com/">Official Website</a></strong> of Asurion to make a phone claim request.</li>
<li style="padding-left: 30px;">To start over with this click on &#8220;Claim Now&#8221; button</li>
<li style="padding-left: 30px;">Now select your carrier from the available brands including AT&amp;T, Cricket, Fido, Koodo, Freedom Mobile, nTelox wireless, MetroPCS, Sprint, Rogers, T-Mobile, Telus, Verizon, and Walmart.</li>
<li style="padding-left: 30px;">Complete the further information about the mobile and Asurion plan. This normally includes your name, email, phone number, shipping address, incident details, payment mode.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-phoneclaim-com-asurion-phone-claim/">How to Submit an Asurion Phone Claim</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-phoneclaim-com-asurion-phone-claim/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy Maui Jim Sunglasses for Both Men and Women</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mauijim-com-maui-jim-sunglasses/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mauijim-com-maui-jim-sunglasses/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 17:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3294</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Open www.mauijim.com to buy Maui Jim sunglasses for men&#8217;s and women&#8217;s. MauiJim sport sunglasses is also a professional &#38; high-quality product for consumers. Having a long history that starts from the 12th century or earlier in China. The spectacles or glasses were made initially to protect the human eyes from the dazzling and bright light [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mauijim-com-maui-jim-sunglasses/">Buy Maui Jim Sunglasses for Both Men and Women</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Open <span style="color: #0000ff;">www.mauijim.com</span> to buy <em><strong>Maui Jim sunglasses</strong></em> for men&#8217;s and women&#8217;s. MauiJim sport sunglasses is also a professional &amp; high-quality product for consumers. Having a long history that starts from the 12th century or earlier in China. The spectacles or glasses were made initially to protect the human eyes from the dazzling and bright light of the sun. At that time polished gems were used for this purpose.</p>
<blockquote class="modern-quote full"><p>“Putting on a new pair of glasses or sunglasses is a simple way to completely transform your look- just like a new hairstyle.” <cite>Brad Goreski</cite></p></blockquote>
<p>With the passage of time, more modifications and advancements were done to the blinkers for the comfort of human eyes. In present tense people have made categories out of these spectacles. The glasses which are worn for the <strong>protection of eyes from harmful rays of sunlight</strong> and its blazing effect. Are called “Sunglasses” or “Shades”. The only purpose of sunglasses is not to provide shield effect for eyes. But they also have a very important role in the clothing and styling of one’s personality.</p>
<p>Sunglasses give a new and awesome look to the face. Furthermore, they add an extra point of confidence to the individual identity of a person. Moreover, these <strong>little comfortable gadgets that sit on the nose</strong> and hold on to ears. Enable the user to do any work in the bright sunshine without having to wrinkle the eyes.</p>
<h2>www.mauijim.com Features &amp; Variety</h2>
<p>Sunglasses give a new and awesome look to the face. They add an extra point of confidence to the individual identity of a person. Moreover, these little comfortable gadgets that sit on the nose and hold on to ears, enable the user to do any work in the <strong>bright sunshine without having to wrinkle the eyes</strong>. Despite these uses, sunglasses are also worn by people and famous personalities as a personal identity or unique style.</p>
<p>One of the famous and great the source of sunglasses which offers a colossal variety and styles of shades for people of different tastes and regions is known as “Maui Jim”. Situated in Maui, Hawaii, the Company has been a recognized <strong>seller of high-quality sun wear glasses</strong>. The industry took a startup in 1980 through merchandising of sunglasses on a beach in Lahaina, Hawaii. Later on, the Company introduced ‘Polarized Plus lenses” and presented new, and classic selection of glasses.</p>
<h3>Types of Maui Jim Sunglasses</h3>
<p>Being a premium sunglasses supplier Maui Jim has been selected by industry experts as the best sunglass Company for the second successive year. The company provides a huge collection of different types of sunglasses for different people. It has also got the award for best <strong>Sports Sunglasses</strong> Brand (women). Customers can shop at Maui Jim without any doubt about the quality and services since Maui Jim has always kept the promise of providing <strong>superior lens technology</strong> and high product quality. One more feature of the company which is loved by the customers is their quick fix service within three days for major defects in the product and even for tiny repairs.</p>
<p><strong>Shopping at Maui Jim</strong> can be made possible by registering online. The user has to click the “login” and then “Create Account” button on the main website. After filling the personal and login information the user has to click “submit” and the account is created. After registration, all the categories of glasses can be viewed and chosen by simple clicking. The product page lists down the reviews of customers and details of products.</p>
<p>There is <strong>another useful feature</strong> provided on the website of Maui Jim, which is “checkout” option, which enables the clients to see the difference before and after wearing the glasses just by entering their Gift Card number or VIP Card Number and pin.</p>
<p>Maui Jim Gift card service gives the customers an <strong>ease in buying the best glasses</strong> for their friends and family. The company rocks in the eyes of customers by offering two years of warranty on the product after purchase!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mauijim-com-maui-jim-sunglasses/">Buy Maui Jim Sunglasses for Both Men and Women</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-mauijim-com-maui-jim-sunglasses/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marisota Provides All Types of Fashion Clothing to Customers</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-marisota-co-uk-marisota-fashion-clothing/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-marisota-co-uk-marisota-fashion-clothing/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 23:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3221</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Visit www.marisota.co.uk to shop fashion dresses. Marisota is shopping platform where users can find clothing and other accessories.  Clothes are an integral part of life, and the shopping of clothes has to be done by everyone. Regardless of their gender, age or taste. Many people find it interesting to go shopping for their clothes. Moreover, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-marisota-co-uk-marisota-fashion-clothing/">Marisota Provides All Types of Fashion Clothing to Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Visit <span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.marisota.co.uk</em></span> to shop fashion dresses. Marisota is shopping platform where users can find clothing and other accessories.  <strong>Clothes are an integral part of life</strong>, and the shopping of clothes has to be done by everyone. Regardless of their gender, age or taste. Many people find it interesting to go shopping for their clothes. Moreover, they try on different dresses and accessories by and then buying it after getting completely satisfied.</p>
<blockquote class="modern-quote full"><p>“When I buy clothes, I like to buy them in outfits so I know they go together. I like a very simple, natural style. I never like to be the attention getter, I like to come under the radar and be cool about my look, very classic and stylish. I’m not into fads.” <cite>Rena Sofer</cite></p></blockquote>
<h2>www.marisota.co.uk Features &amp; Introduction</h2>
<p>While some people are so reluctant about shopping. They just want to get the best quality outfits and dresses of their choice, size, and color to reach their doorstep without doing any struggle. For such kind of people, online shopping is a blessing. But online shopping sometimes doesn’t give the best results. Because, if <strong>someone is not good at selecting things</strong> from a visual representation or if they keep trying new websites every time. So, Marisota tries to solve all the quality and trust issues of customers. Furthermore, it enables them shopping in a comfortable environment without any doubt about the price and aspects.</p>
<p>Marisota is a direct home shopping company set up in the United Kingdom in 1875 by James David Williams. It is a top rated company in its category. Besides to that, it is <strong>first ever company to make use of UK’s parcel</strong> service to deliver customers’ orders. After introducing the feature of delivering the orders or products to customer doorsteps let the company grow very rapidly and it became the UK’s most famous home shopping company.</p>
<h3>Fashion Clothing on Marisota</h3>
<p>Marisota has also used the internet in the best way to facilitate its customers by providing online shopping. The online service of Marisota enables its clients to buy top quality brands and a huge collection of classy and fashionable clothes at reasonable prices. Their <strong>product list covers all varieties, styles, and categories</strong> of clothes including women and men clothes, sportswear, shoes, lingerie, swimwear, accessories and much more.</p>
<p>For being an <strong>online customer of Marisota</strong>, the customers need to get registered them first. The online registration is an easy and quick process. At first, an email address and a password need to be entered, then the customer has to provide their personal information such as full name, sir name, title, date of birth, phone number etc. The next step is to enter the address or location details for order delivery process. In the end, the registrar has to accept the terms and conditions of the website and must go through the data protection notice once.</p>
<p>Hitting the ‘Finish’ button opens up a new window where a chart appears with the title of “Available to spend”. The <strong>chart displays the amount of available credit</strong> that the customer can use to shop through his account on sign-up.</p>
<p>After registration, the <strong>shopping procedure</strong> is as easy as clicking the mouse. Just click the desired clothes and fill up the size, color, fitting and quantity details and visit the checkout page. There is a 20% off on the very first purchase of products. The payment can be done using Visa card, Maestro or Master card. All the information is secured via Norton secured to ensure customer trust.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-marisota-co-uk-marisota-fashion-clothing/">Marisota Provides All Types of Fashion Clothing to Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-marisota-co-uk-marisota-fashion-clothing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>PETCO Provides Your Pets Grooming  Foods, Create Account to get Rewards &#038; Coupons</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-petco-com-rewards-coupons/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-petco-com-rewards-coupons/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 17:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3180</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.Petco.com is private pet grooming, supplies, &#38; products retailer, Visit website to create account and get rewards &#38; coupons, promotions, and discounts offers. The bond between pets and people is unique in most aspects; for one thing, it doesn’t involve endless chatter, you don’t have to resolve long-standing grudges every single day, and on a [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-petco-com-rewards-coupons/">PETCO Provides Your Pets Grooming  Foods, Create Account to get Rewards &#038; Coupons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.Petco.com</em></span> is private pet grooming, supplies, &amp; products retailer, Visit website to create account and get rewards &amp; coupons, promotions, and discounts offers. The bond between pets and people is unique in most aspects; for one thing, it doesn’t <em><strong>involve endless chatter</strong></em>, you don’t have to resolve long-standing grudges every single day, and on a comparatively more pessimistic note, you have to provide for them.</p>
<p>But the <strong>cost of their care is nothing</strong> compared to the sense of satisfaction and pleasure their constant company brings to you; only a few joys compare to that of pet parenting.</p>
<blockquote class="modern-quote full"><p>‘If I had a pound for every time my dog made me smile I’d be a millionaire.’<cite>Anonymous</cite></p></blockquote>
<p>Petco has a mission of enhancing and empowering your relationship with your pets leading to a much better quality life for the innocent creatures who can’t voice their own needs and wants. Guided by a stand-alone motto ‘Healthier Pets, Happier people, Better World’ <strong>Petco strives to help you provide the most premium care</strong> to your pets. Petco offers foods and treats, cages, carriers, clean-up supplies, odor controls, harnesses, collars, leashes, grooming and bathing stuff, perches, playground, play stands and a lot more for your pets. With over half a decade’s experience of pet care, www.petco.com  helps your pets thrive.</p>
<h3>www.Petco.com Free Member Account</h3>
<p>If you are new to Petco, signing up for a free Petco account is a great idea. You’ll receive offers and benefits that will make you a permanent customer at Petco. You get to <strong>place your orders online</strong> with a single ‘log in&#8217;, enjoy a 5% discount on every purchase, track your order, check your Pals Rewards, and a $5 reward for a purchase of every $100.</p>
<h3>PALS REWARDS</h3>
<p>It is a wonderful way to <strong>earn rewards while shopping</strong> for your pet’s favorite food items and other treats. Once you sign up for Pals Rewards membership in store, you will have to create an online account linked to the same Pals Rewards Account number to be entitled to the following perks:</p>
<ol>
<li>Update your account profile</li>
<li>Track earning status</li>
<li>Claim reward dollars</li>
</ol>
<p>PALS members enjoy exclusive advantages listed below</p>
<ul>
<li>5 Reward dollars for every $100 spent.</li>
<li>Bonus offers to earn rewards even faster</li>
<li>Birthday surprises for your pets.</li>
<li>Daily savings on hundreds of products</li>
<li>Exclusive discounts and coupons.</li>
</ul>
<h4>PETCO COUPONS AND PROMO CODES</h4>
<p>This section features all the latest coupon and promotions in an easily accessible way. The Featured Offers are sure to make your jaw drop:</p>
<ol>
<li>Buy 1, Get 1 free deal on leap bound dog toys</li>
<li>$650 in coupon, Ask for a New Companion Care Pack.</li>
<li>Free shipping on repeat delivery</li>
</ol>
<p>One of the latest offers is <strong>free shipping on $29</strong> with the promo code ‘weekend’. Petco coupons can be redeemed for all types of purchases, in store or online. Make sure you read all the details of every promo before you use them at check out.</p>
<h4>PETCO GROOMING</h4>
<p>It is well known a fact that no matter how cute, a dirty and disheveled pet can make own your home a mess. Using the <strong>most advanced facilities</strong> and by ensuring meticulous standards, petco.com  strives to provide your pets with the best grooming care possible so that you can enjoy the company of your pet to the fullest. Each <strong>grooming session</strong> starts with a <strong>7-point check system</strong>. You can book an appointment with your favorite stylist and enjoy a service that is worth spending your penny on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-petco-com-rewards-coupons/">PETCO Provides Your Pets Grooming  Foods, Create Account to get Rewards &#038; Coupons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-petco-com-rewards-coupons/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Kings Lane Serves Furnishing One Wants But Couldn&#8217;t Find</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/one-kings-lane-furniture-www-onekingslane-com/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/one-kings-lane-furniture-www-onekingslane-com/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3179</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>One Kings Lane Furniture is a website where the users can buy or inspire with Luxury furniture. Visit www.onekingslane.com and check for home decor items. The New Year must have brought new yearnings for a wholly new interior and home décor. All those old style furnitures were thrown like an unwanted clutter into your living [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/one-kings-lane-furniture-www-onekingslane-com/">One Kings Lane Serves Furnishing One Wants But Couldn&#8217;t Find</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>One Kings Lane Furniture</strong></em> is a website where the users can buy or inspire with Luxury furniture. Visit <em><span style="color: #0000ff;">www.onekingslane.com</span></em> and check for home decor items. The New Year must have brought <em><strong>new yearnings for a wholly new interior and home décor</strong></em>. All those old style furnitures were thrown like an unwanted clutter into your living room; the colors so vehement that you feel suffocated the contrasts so odd that you question your own taste, and the fabric so wore out that ‘comfort’ seems like a word out of another world.</p>
<p>Oh, yeah, this might be the description of your ‘once-cherished abode’ if ignored for a long time in terms of renovation. Well, <strong>it’s time for you to rid yourself of all that mess</strong> and gear up for an all new décor. But wait for a second; you need to be inspired before you decide on your course of action! The one and only place where you can safely repose your trust are One Kings Lane.</p>
<h2><strong>One Kings Lane Furniture Offers &amp; Discount</strong></h2>
<p>No matter what you are looking for, One Kings Lane has got you covered in every possible way. With a full-blown exquisite range of exuberant furniture and other home décor items, One King Lane lets you infuse your personality into your abode in a way that leaves every spectator awed. The enchanting interior, eclectic pieces of art, sumptuously soft beddings, elegantly shaped chandeliers, splendidly crafted vases, exquisite rugs and a <strong>lot more is there for you to discover and lay your hands on</strong>. Just check in to <a href="http://www.onekingslane.com/">www.onekingslane.com</a> and delve into a world of décor fantasy.</p>
<p>You can shop by style such as Parisian Chic, Coastal Charm, Modern Glamour, American Classic, European Rustic, etc. or you can browse the <strong>collection for the individual rooms</strong> of your house such as for the living, dining, bed, guest, kids and even outdoor. Whatever you purchase at One Kings Lane is bound to be a perfect blend of grace and elegance.</p>
<h3>SIGN UP FOR A FREE ACCOUNT</h3>
<p>Want to get regular updates on the new arrivals of your most coveted items? Sign up for a free account whereby you are subscribed to email alerts of new offers and promotions. The email alerts bug you? Just want to have an account for easier checkout and not for email alerts? Unsubscribe to it with a mere click.</p>
<h3>ONE KINGS LANE GIFT CARDS</h3>
<p>Want somebody to live their dreams? Give them One Kings Lane <strong>E- gift cards</strong> and they can never stop thanking you. Gift cards are delivered to the recipient with a customized message from the sender. Moreover, one can redeem it for any purchase. They come in <strong>$25 &#8211; $500 prices</strong> and guess what, they never expire!</p>
<h3>ONE KINGS LANE STUDIO</h3>
<p>You might have the vision but still not the astute skill and sense. Which it takes to blend pieces of art in the most compelling way, such that everything speaks for itself. One Kings Lane Studio is one way to inspire you with ideas and schemes that are bound to make your home a haven of warmth and indulgence, where <strong>everything is a perfect blend of beauty and elegance</strong>, and where even the tiniest details perfectly embody the one who dwells there. A face to face session with one of the top designers and stylists is sure to turn your dream of a perfect house into a reality. What’s more, the consultation is absolutely free.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/one-kings-lane-furniture-www-onekingslane-com/">One Kings Lane Serves Furnishing One Wants But Couldn&#8217;t Find</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/one-kings-lane-furniture-www-onekingslane-com/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pets4Home for Selling Dogs, Cats is Best Classified Site in UK on Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/pets4home-uk-www-pets4homes-co-uk/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/pets4home-uk-www-pets4homes-co-uk/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 16:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3178</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Pets4Home UK is best place to find online sales of dogs &#38; cats. Why keep pets, dogs &#38; cats? The website www.pets4homes.co.uk allows to place your ad online. Well, for one thing, they make for perfect companions because they don’t hold the same long-standing grudges that humans do. They love you unconditionally, without any judgment [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/pets4home-uk-www-pets4homes-co-uk/">Pets4Home for Selling Dogs, Cats is Best Classified Site in UK on Sale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Pets4Home UK</strong> is best place to find online sales of dogs &amp; cats. Why keep pets, dogs &amp; cats? The website <em><span style="color: #0000ff;">www.pets4homes.co.uk</span></em> allows to place your ad online. Well, for one thing, they make for perfect companions because they don’t hold the same long-standing grudges that humans do. <strong>They love you unconditionally, without any judgment</strong> and they teach you compassion and accountability.</p>
<p>And above all, they are a source of comfort and pleasure. Can anything substitute for the magic of the calming purr of your cat as it rests on your lap? Or the unstoppable lick of your dog when it crawls all over you every time you walk in? No matter what pet you have, cat, dog, fish, hamsters, parrots, to name a few, each of them has its unique way of calming and pleasing you.</p>
<h3>PETS4HOME UK for Selling Pets Online</h3>
<p>If you don’t have dogs, cats andpets, there are at least a thousand reasons for you to get one. They help you deal with a rough day and in times of stress and depression, they actually empathize. They might actually not, but even the feeling of their presence, in a sense, helps you share your burden with them. You can actually pour all your heart in front of them and still not run the risk of getting judged and misunderstood. <strong>Only having someone to cuddle can work wonders in uplifting your mood.</strong></p>
<p>Worried about where to get one? Well look no further, <a href="http://www.pets4homes.co.uk/">www.pets4homes.co.uk</a> caters to the tastes and preferences of all the people when it comes to choosing your pets? <strong><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Pets4home.co.uk</span></em> is a leading pet advertising website</strong> where you can sell and buy pets of all kinds and at the best bargains.</p>
<h3>www.pets4homes.co.uk User Account</h3>
<p>Go to ‘My Account’ section at the top of the home page of the website, click ‘Registration’, you are directed to a new page. Fill out all the fields with accurate information. You can sign up using any of the following account types, the details of which are given in a separate dialog box at the bottom.</p>
<ol>
<li>Standard account</li>
<li>Breeder account</li>
<li>Rescue center account</li>
</ol>
<h4>BENEFITS</h4>
<p>A Pets4Home account is mandatory for you to be able to post your own pet advertisements of sale, adoption, wanted or stud. Moreover, signing up provides you with <strong>unlimited and exclusive offers and promotions</strong>. Some of the most amazing benefits of a Pets4Home account include;</p>
<ul>
<li>Access to amazing offer</li>
<li>Save your favorite adverts</li>
<li>Creating ads without providing basic info again and again.</li>
<li>Getting to reply all the ads with one ‘sign in’</li>
<li>Upload as many photos as you want for your adverts</li>
<li>Subscribe to Pets4Home newsletter</li>
</ul>
<h5><strong>Pets4Home UK &#8211; </strong>BUY AND SELL</h5>
<p>You can post your own ad by signing up for an account as described above. If you are here to buy, check out the ‘Latest Adverts’ or go for type specific search. Following types of pets are available;</p>
<ul>
<li>Rabbits</li>
<li>Rodents</li>
<li>Cats</li>
<li>Dogs</li>
<li>Fish</li>
<li>Reptile</li>
<li>Birds</li>
<li>Poultry</li>
</ul>
<p>Don’t want to bother with all the available offers? Look for your own favorite right away: choose the pet type, breed type, and location and hit the ‘Search’ button. You will get the <strong>most relevant advertisements</strong> saving your precious time.</p>
<h6>DOG ADVICE</h6>
<p>Want to get expert advice on how to provide the best care for your pets? The ‘Dog Advice’ section of Pets4Home has got you covered. Just click on the three horizontal bars on the home page, go to the ‘Dogs Advice’ section and get <strong>ready to be inspired with brilliant tips and tricks</strong> to tackle the needs and wants of your pets. What’s more, it’s absolutely free!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/pets4home-uk-www-pets4homes-co-uk/">Pets4Home for Selling Dogs, Cats is Best Classified Site in UK on Sale</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/pets4home-uk-www-pets4homes-co-uk/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Old Navy Making Fashion Accessible to Everyone</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-oldnavy-com-old-navy-clothing/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-oldnavy-com-old-navy-clothing/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 21:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3148</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>www.oldnavy.com to shop Old Navy clothes online, the Old Navy clothing makes the fashion accessible to everyone. Buy what you would like from clothing to toys. Over the course of time, fashion has changed tremendously, and it still continues to change every day. Things go out of style, new things come in vogue but one [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-oldnavy-com-old-navy-clothing/">Old Navy Making Fashion Accessible to Everyone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0000ff;"><em>www.oldnavy.com</em></span> to shop Old Navy clothes online, the Old Navy clothing makes the fashion accessible to everyone. Buy what you would like from clothing to toys. Over the course of time, <em><strong>fashion has changed tremendously</strong></em>, and it still continues to change every day. Things go out of style, new things come in vogue but one thing stays the same; people’s desire of looking fashionable. Nowadays, this desire is ubiquitous among people of all social standings not just restricted to the elite class.</p>
<p>The ways to acquit it, however, varies largely across not only different classes of the society but also among individuals on the basis of their tastes and preferences. Thus, the need to <strong>bring designs and trends well-suited not just to everyone’s taste</strong> but to their pocket is just as pressing as the need to introduce novelty and inventiveness.</p>
<h2>www.oldnavy.com Features &amp; Offers</h2>
<p>People want to change which is why fashion designers always rise to the occasion, introducing <strong>styles that are unique and novel</strong>. As such, you won’t find scarcity of variety and creativity when you go out for shopping. What might be actually cumbersome for most of you is the price that you have to pay for all those trendy clothes? All the customer friendly policies of the leading brands fail to satisfy you when it comes to sparing your pocket a little. That’s where Old Navy steps in, one of the leading brands owned by Gap, Inc. Old navy features clothes for men, women and even toddlers at the most reasonable prices. Go on to <a href="http://www.oldnavy.com/">www.oldnavy.com</a> and enjoy amazing discounts and offers.</p>
<h3>SIGN UP FOR OLD NAVY ACCOUNT</h3>
<p>Why waste time entering your billing and shipping information again and again when you can enjoy easier checkout and <strong>more convenient features</strong> by registering for Old Navy account with your email address. Yes, it’s that easy. Once you sign up for an account you can easily track your orders and check your gift card balance and credit card rewards. You are also enrolled for exclusive promotions and offers. You can check out your rewards by clicking on ‘Your Account’ section on the top of the main page.</p>
<h3>OLD NAVY VISA CARD</h3>
<p>Old Navy Visa Card has multiple ways of rewarding you; you earn points whenever you shop at any of the Gap brands, in store or online. You get <strong>15% discount on your first purchase</strong> with your Old Navy Visa Card.  Some of the most popular rewards are;</p>
<ul>
<li>5 points for every $1 spent in any of the Gap brands, in-store or online.</li>
<li>1 points for every $1 purchase everywhere VISA is accepted.</li>
<li>A reward of $5 for every 500 points</li>
</ul>
<p>The Visa Card holders earn extra rewards when they use Old Navy Visa Card to make payments at brands even outside of Gap, Inc.</p>
<h3>NAVYIST CARD</h3>
<p>This is the highest cardholder status at Old Navy which entitles you to even more rewards, more exclusive offers, and promotions. You can <strong>qualify for NAVYIST card</strong> when you earn 5000 points with your Old Navy Visa Card. The NAVYIST cardholders enjoy free shipping when they shop online at any of the Gap brands including Gap, Banana Republic, Athleta and Old Navy.</p>
<h3>www.oldnavy.com GIFT CARDS</h3>
<p>Why fuss so much about the perfect gift when you can give them the chance to select their own at one of the leading brands? Gift cards are an extremely <strong>easy way to spare you the trouble of roaming all those aisles</strong> with no clue what to pick up. Gift cards come in both printed and electronic forms and can be utilized in-stores and online. However printed or traditional cards can be redeemed only in the United States.</p>
<p>The gift cards can be directly shipped to the recipient you want to send it to or they can be delivered to you so that you can give them to your loved one in person.  the gift card can be used at any of the four Gap, Inc brands i.e. Old Navy, Gap, Banana Republic, Athleta.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/www-oldnavy-com-old-navy-clothing/">Old Navy Making Fashion Accessible to Everyone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/www-oldnavy-com-old-navy-clothing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nordstrom Bringing Style to Life</title>
		<link>https://www.thefinancials.net/nordstrom-stores-www-nordstrom-com/</link>
		<comments>https://www.thefinancials.net/nordstrom-stores-www-nordstrom-com/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jacob]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Shopping]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.theguidance.info/?p=3139</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Nordstrom store offer a number of items for online shopping at www.nordstrom.com, Get clothing, jewelry, makeup &#38; all other accessories for women, men and children. Obsession with the latest trends and an astute sense of pride in one’s own appearance do not necessarily equate to vanity and frivolity, rather fashion can actually be a form [...]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/nordstrom-stores-www-nordstrom-com/">Nordstrom Bringing Style to Life</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>Nordstrom store</strong></em> offer a number of items for online shopping at <em><span style="color: #0000ff;">www.nordstrom.com</span></em>, Get clothing, jewelry, makeup &amp; all other accessories for women, men and children. Obsession with the latest trends and an astute sense of pride in one’s own appearance do not necessarily equate to vanity and frivolity, rather fashion can actually be a form of expression, a revelation of who you are. This concept has gained even more strength and momentum in the 21st century.</p>
<h2>Nordstrom Store Offers &amp; Rewards</h2>
<p>Today more and more people are <strong>realizing the importance of fashion and style</strong> in boosting confidence and well-being of an individual. However, none of those fabulous fancy clothes are going to do any wonder if they don’t fit and suit you perfectly well. Make fashion your personal statement and incorporate your personality into the styles you adopt, and you are bound to glow and shine.</p>
<p>With a relentless spirit to provide the customers with their own unique fashionable identity, <strong>Nordstrom strives to bring style to life for its customers.</strong> Featuring clothes, shoes, and accessories from some of the tops of the leading brands such as Adidas, Nike, TOM FORD, J.Crew, Madewell, etc. Nordstrom has over a hundred years’ history of providing the most versatile range of clothes, shoes, and accessories for men, women, and kids.</p>
<h3>WHY SIGN UP NORDSTROM?</h3>
<p>There are plenty of reasons for you to sign up at Nordstrom; for one thing, it makes your shopping faster and easier. To create an account at Nordstrom, click “Your Account’ at the top of any page of Nordstrom, <strong>enter your email address and password</strong> and you are all set to enjoy the following exclusive benefits:</p>
<ul>
<li>Customer review</li>
<li>Express Checkouts</li>
<li>Track your order</li>
<li>Order history</li>
<li>Address book</li>
<li>Email alerts</li>
</ul>
<h4>WISHLIST</h4>
<p>The wish list allows you to save all your favorite items in one place where you can view it conveniently whenever you want just with an easy ‘Sign In’. Not only this, you also get to <strong>share your favorites with your friends and family</strong> so you can receive the perfect gifts. You can also access the wish list of your most imitate friends and relatives so that you have a clear idea of their choice when you opt for a gift.</p>
<h4>NORDSTROM GIFT CARDS</h4>
<p>Choosing the perfect gift for your favorite people on the planet can be really hectic and might even drive you crazy but that’s where Nordstrom comes in. Nordstrom <strong>gift cards ensure that your loved ones can get exactly what they want</strong>. There are those that can send by mail and those that can be sent directly by email. All of them can be redeemed online, in stores or by phone. With Business gift cards, you can reward your colleagues and employees in the most stylish way.</p>
<h4>NORDSTROM PERSONAL STYLISTS</h4>
<p>Who knows you better than you? Well, the stylists at Nordstrom can confidently claim to know your closet at least just as well as you know, if not more. The <strong>free and frank advice of Nordstrom Personal Stylists</strong> makes your shopping for clothes, shoes, and accessories seem extremely convenient.  They enlighten you on not only what’s in vogue but also on what would suit you best. You can book an appointment online or by contacting your nearest store. Nordstrom will make sure that you get the best tips on mixing, matching and complementing.  The appointments are of the following types</p>
<ul>
<li>Quick Update</li>
<li>Trend Review</li>
<li>For All Appearances</li>
<li>The Custom Consult</li>
</ul>
<p>Nordstrom helps you possess style and not just fashion; its exquisite collection of clothes, shoes, and accessories are bound to give you the look you’ll absolutely love. Just log on to www.nordstrom.com and get inspired.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/nordstrom-stores-www-nordstrom-com/">Nordstrom Bringing Style to Life</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thefinancials.net/">TheFinancials</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thefinancials.net/nordstrom-stores-www-nordstrom-com/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
